Okay, I'm like, I look a pretty, pretty, pretty moth.
Hi.
Oh, yeah, I got my coffee.
Oh, shit.
I keep hitting the button, shit.
Excuse me.
Hi, guys.
What's up?
I'm doing a quick walk.
Got my coffee.
Getting my cigars.
Same story.
I supposedly stole them, by the way.
I'm still lacking.
Okay.
Hi.
You bet.
How are you?
Hi.
All right.
Can I get, um, to, uh, switch up, please?
Thank you.
Have a nice day.
Hey.
Hi.
Where the pet store goes to get a goldfish?
I'm not at the pet store.
I was at the liquor store, but there is a pet smart or a pet go.
Hi, Nick.
Hi, everybody.
What's up?
You can go sit on a bench over here like look at the view. It's a pretty beautiful day actually
The water is like blue. It's health. Uh-oh hitting butts
Hi everybody. Okay, so let me see. I'm gonna go sit down. Just give me a minute. Okay, this is green light go
Okay
So yeah, this is like the beautiful
Little park right here. I don't know what it's called. I don't see what it's called. It's called park
Okay, let's see
Oh, it says park hours.
So close the tent here, but there's no like gates or anything.
I'm like, oh, you see, oh, here we go.
Okay, there we go.
Okay, I keep cutting out, I'm sorry.
Okay, yeah, well here, here we are.
It's really beautiful actually, like a park.
A lot of people walk their dogs here.
We'll get closer to the water too.
So clear.
Can you see what the park is though?
Oh, I don't remember exactly.
It says this is the William Zugler Plaza.
From 1990
Shit, he pressed the button. Oh, you know. Hey, um, so
This was landscaped
Architected pretty nice actually
But I would say that it would suck to live on there like these other side of the building right here
You can't really see the ocean. Can you see the ocean view?
You can walk a little closer, but I'm gonna sit down for a second and fix it. Oh, he's hot
Got some dolphins here
Q-Page and okay
Okay, there you go.
All right, okay, let's see.
See the ocean behind me?
But I call ocean view, okay.
How's everyone, how's everyone's night?
Hold on a second.
People take the plaque down and then people don't,
people take the plaques and use them for drugs
and melt them for drugs, oh my God.
Hey Nancy, reality sister Nancy.
Benette posted something good, I wanna check it out.
Get a fish tank? Well, Samman has an empty one. Maybe he can help me out. He can send it to me.
Fish are hard, so I mean, it's like, you know, it's not very hard to care, but I remember I used
to take care of a fish at the office I worked at. And we have the beta fish, or beta fish, I call it
now. And it was a really pretty blue little fish. And it was like, and they come in these little
It's like they eat the roots.
You don't even need to feed them
because they eat on the roots of this plant
that are like on top of the thing, right?
And so I forgot the name of the fish.
I think it was bubbles or something like that.
But one of my jobs is like to clean that fish tank.
So I would take it to the office sink
and pour it out as much as I could,
and then clean the rocks off.
I mean, I try to put the fish in like another thing.
but it was always hectic.
Like a few times I dropped the fish
into the garbage disposal.
I had to fish the fish out of the garbage disposal.
That's not pleasant, but the fish was always revived.
But the thing was with the, okay,
the thing was with the, then I cleaned it,
it smelled like human weight.
It was like the worst smell of my life, you know?
Yeah, everybody. How are you? Look at the shade you just realized. Yeah, I shaved a few days ago
So I don't look so old. I'm just being told constantly. Oh my god. He's
Teary and think so much. I haven't deteriorated if I deteriorated it was way before I started doing my stuff
I mean, if I'd be scary if I just hear more
I thought I was yeah, isn't it bad? It was so gross. It smells so bad. Hmm
So fish are kind of gross
And then like, you know, we used to have like, you know, we've been like friends with fish tanks and stuff, like, and I just remember these like
The scary fighting fish that would like eat all the other fish in the tank
And they would keep like they would buy this fish and then all the other fish would be all of a sudden all dead
That pretty view. You can go closer to the water since it's clear to there. Mockdown. Okay. And there's nobody here
It's like a band. It's like I'm the only person. I have the whole park to myself
Like I could just do like a Sarah. I could like, you know
a cult ritual out here and nobody would even care if my pants are falling down a little bit.
My belt needs to be tight. Okay, let me go back and do that before I have a very embarrassing
situation on camera. Okay, here I am. I'm frozen. I'm so handsome. I cover their egg. I know. I mean,
it's like, you know, if you see these pictures of me, like even baked clips too, I like don't even
Well, I don't know. He was like talking about anything. Oh, I was that I was playing like some TV show from England from like this
And he's like, wait, is this a more AI slop?
Pretty annoying a slice of those birthday. I know you love sliced alone. Wow. He's a cancer. Okay. Yeah, that's right
My mom's birthday too. Yeah, and it was just I annex his birthday. It was just
Lisa Jordan's birthday. It's kind of crazy. There's a lot of birthday. Yeah, it's good right now
It keeps my phone keeps my phone keeps cutting down. Let me make that bigger. There we go. Okay
If I turn it like this, do you see more?
Okay, here we go.
Let me put up my pants for a while.
I mean, I'm wearing a belt, but I think I'm,
can I just walk my belt?
I don't know, it was on the top, not the tightest one.
Okay, perfect.
Now look at this tree too.
This is a really pretty tree.
Okay.
Now we can go for a walk-up.
Okay, let me look.
There we go.
I'm sorry, I know it keeps freezing.
50th anniversary of Rocky.
You know what I keep hearing, I keep hearing that da-da-da, da-da-da, da-da-da, da-da-da.
I hear that song all the time, but you know where that song is played? It's so weird.
It's on that comedian, on that thing, the AI comedian that they're trying to make us think was like a real comedian in like the 80s.
You love the trees, don't they pretty? They're really pretty trees, huh?
Yeah, there's, you can look him up his name. I'll show him when I get home. His name is Roy J.
Okay guys anybody heard of Roy Jay besides me telling you about Roy Jay or hearing about him in the past year
Because last year like oh my god
Last year. Oh my god
So here we go with the water. It's really pretty day actually
Okay, so Roy Jay is like
Someone posted on like a 4chan or something like oh, they're like, oh, there's a demon from the past
Trying to rewrite himself into history
He's like, do you recognize this guy?
He's pretty soon you will.
I think you'll remember him from your childhood.
Kind of weird, right?
And kind of calling him a demon or something.
And then all of a sudden, oh.
And then, sorry, then all of a sudden, Roy J.
His name is Roy J.
Roy, but it's J-J-A-Y, yeah.
Okay, so here's what he was like.
He sounds like Robin Williams, where he's British, right?
But he has like a Robin Williams delivery.
I think there's a boat, so it doesn't appear
when I walk down.
That's pretty nice, huh?
I can see it.
Okay, oh shit.
I seem to like practice.
When you practice, I'm not hitting the button so much.
Okay, there we go.
So there we go.
You can see it looks pretty cool, huh?
Like the white flag, I don't know what the flag's mean,
but there's, yeah.
There's like a lot of people walking around.
Okay.
So have you ever heard of this comedian?
He like, he walks around the stage,
like he has Tourette syndrome or something like that.
When they oh shit
When cancel
When they when he walks out on the stage
He was on all these all the all of a sudden the others a Wikipedia page and all these old British TV shows when he walks out on the stage
He's like kind of like dancing his eyes are like all weird
His hands are he worries with his white gloves like Michael Jackson or but he were two of them
so one more of Michael Jackson does and
And he says
really dumb jokes
He goes, he goes, oh, I met, I met this guy, and I said, are you a pole, Walter?
And he goes, no, I'm German, but how do you know my name was Walter?
Okay, everything is like really dumb, right?
Yeah, it's like the worst joke.
And then he goes, slither, spook.
Does he even remember that comedian from the 80s from England?
And it's like all, like, it's like all weird.
I mean, it's like, and it's like you know the secret.
I know the secret.
The secret is they're fucking with us like they always do.
Yeah, there was no Roy J.
I mean, it's like, and then there's people like,
and all of a sudden there's pictures of the pages appearing
and old things, but then you can see, like it's AI.
You can tell because I don't know if they're trying
to make it obvious or something, but.
At some point he grows like six fingers on his hand his eyes go all around his face
And they're like, oh, it's just it's here. I watched a lot of 80 stuff. I watched I watched beta
I'm not you know, not not beta beta max. I watch all that stuff and
I've never seen things like that happen, but like where it's like, yeah, I've seen like, you know, like not the best quality
But I don't see like the eyes
Hopping around and stuff. Okay, so here's a restaurant. They used to go there with my dad
We it was called Captain's kids. We didn't know the owner of it. Actually, it's called Captain's kids
Being there for you good job, but I'm not gonna get through right now
If I coffee there's somebody's bike
There you go, okay, I'm gonna
Walk home. Okay. I'm walking home. So this is like the bike path
See how you guys see here's this is the
Captain's kids
so it's a really nice little area down here but it's a beautiful day that makes a difference you
know the sky is so blue it's a beautiful day it's a beautiful day don't let it go it smells really
good too but it's expensive like okay the thing also the roger is they play the rocky theme when he
comes out and i'm like how did he get the rocky theme to use yeah it's for captain kids see yours
Calamari steak, hamburger, cheeseburger,
tilapia, Pacific snapper, catfish,
Alaskan cod, or salmon.
I had the salmon before, so it's the best.
It's all the best.
I like, I mean, I do, like, really good,
you know, I like fish taco stuff.
They have good cocktails and stuff.
I mean, okay, I know this is so annoying.
I wish I had seen it fix my settings,
so it doesn't, like, keep shutting down.
I'm gonna hold my phone different, I think.
There we are.
Yeah, okay.
So, there's all these condos, there's beer.
Somebody walking a dog. Yeah, so I just lip you blocks away from here. Hey, there's ocean snake
I can't read your comment, but thank you so much for coming. Oh should say
Yeah
So how's everyone I mean it's like
Yeah, it's got it's gotten a little bit better. I think but I don't know
I'm everyone's always mad at me for some reason or another I can never get like a
consensus of like peace it always has to be like
Musical chair sometimes with me, but I'm happy we got 17 people in the chat. Nice
It's a little walk
Yeah, I
Do you want to let you know check out my community ball because I'm doing these
These these trading cards
they're kind of like
Based on the lore and the characters and different stuff of my universe or whatever
But I've read is I've gone through several designs of them
To make them like really cool
And so
They're it's kind of a game of the gamified system. You can check it out on codecs. They're going to the collection
but if you want to um
Get awarded like special cards. So the first special card is called the troll king. You can see what it looks like
But i'm gonna like release some official ones
Hopefully i'll get them in print some prints soon too
but um
I also want to make it like a game out of it. See what pickets bigger, but
like uh
you know, I I kind of
Not Pokemon, but you know, I didn't imagine the gathering a little bit, but I don't know. I think I like collecting stuff
I used to collect this stuff called marble masterpiece. They're really cool
Marvel cards
With like these really they're glossy and they were like there's a really good fantasy artist or something that do them
So they're really like pretty and I would collect them and I had some rare ones and stuff
My problem is I had a little brother
He was a little brat, but I know I love my brother.
Yeah, we always laugh about how we used to fight and stuff,
but he used to like, see, I wasn't really into toys or stuff,
but I did like comic books at one point, and video games,
and of course, everyone says, right,
oh, guys, like those.
But he would like, he would like, he would like a huge steal.
I'd find my album and it was like room.
And then all the car, like most of the cars were missing.
He would go and just trade them at school,
like steal my stuff, trade them at school for it, you know?
I get so mad.
And then did I ever get, you know,
did he bring a yelled at?
No.
I always get yelled at.
Don't be so sad.
I mean, it's like, I'm like a type that's like a collector.
Like he never really got, I didn't,
it's like I said, I didn't have his toys.
I didn't have some collectibles.
And he really didn't get into those.
But I had other people that did.
I'd have these like sealed. I had a sealed Marilyn Manson little collectible like action figure that I bought it
But I think I bought it for you like, you know after it was already out
I mean, it's always like I then I go in my room my friend had like just like
He got bored. I think he was open didn't say anything. I mean I said people just don't stand there's people don't consider it's a bad thing
Okay
But anyway, it kind of taught me that you want to like keep something safe you have to fucking lock it up very tight
And then it's like not even worth it sometimes because I don't know how you don't even get to see it
But okay, here we go. I'm crossing the street. Okay. They don't get hit cuz I'm crossing in a red. Okay
okay, ooh
Doppin smoke the pin smoke. Okay. Okay. I'm almost home
so
Look at Elvis Presley is gonna come play here. That's real Elvis. I know he's still alive
Amazing the Elvis will be here and run you don't know
Elvis, do you ever notice Elvis is an anagram for Libs?
You just have to take the E and put it the more in the word.
I don't know how it works exactly this.
I think it turns out that,
I think there's a train right?
I think there's posters all over.
When it's July 25th,
I bet it's just gonna be one of those
fat Elvis impersonators, you know?
I think my, I don't know if my parents
were married by an Elvis impersonator,
but I know they did get married in Vegas
and are shocked on weighing,
but they were traveling around and they're,
camper with their two blended families like five kids kids would like
You know, they would like leave the kids in the
Camper it's really teenagers, you know
They leave the kids in the camper when they went to the 70s late 70s early 80s
And then the kids would get into I'm finally outside the kids would get into like the the alcohol
You shot and they were getting trouble and
My brothers
He's a ginger and he was like super hyperactive
You went to Grayson twice.
Yeah, I'm actually, like I said in Palm Springs,
my dad knows all the celebrity houses there.
And we actually own one of Elvis's properties
and it's rented as like a honeymoon getaway.
But Elvis actually had a house there that he lived in
and it had a mailbox that up until like the 90s,
sometime in the 90s, it said Elvis on it.
And so it was small.
Yeah, I mean, it's just like a house, right?
This is very, very interesting.
Okay, so we are home, okay?
So, let's get up there and see what's going on today.
I cleaned my house yesterday, I cleaned so good.
I go out, clean my kitchen floor,
wash all my dishes, all my clothes.
I sell my bedroom to do.
I want to clean the back for other room view,
but I got most of this stuff from my room clean.
Yeah, it's really cool. We used to see it all the time.
And we lived next door.
In Palm Springs, our house was next door to the Hannah-Barbera Estate.
They were never there, of course, but they had these red gates.
And it's right attached on the same street.
Okay, I'm home.
And like I said, that house used to be owned by Howard Hughes.
His ghost has been seen there.
Palm Springs is a really cool place.
It's like a little oasis in the middle of the desert in Riverside County.
Okay, I'm home.
Hi, babe. You're sitting with me?
Hi, Lola. You can kind of see.
I mean, it's not perfect, but it's like, you know,
it's better than it was. I'm still,
still put your stuff back in.
Yeah, it has like red gates.
Yeah.
He has a jungle room?
Ooh. Okay, let me turn on my computer and,
and I'll, never mind the mouse.
Where's my mousey?
Did you get my mouse, Lola?
No.
It's so funny, people are like,
these cats eat mice.
I'm like, these cats are supposed to eat mice.
I don't know, not eat them.
I mean, they don't sit there and like, you know,
the whole body, I mean, they see the brain.
Okay, sorry, my computer.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna start the computer up.
I need to start.
Okay, here we go.
We're back.
Green carpet, the walls taggy.
Why is it called the jungle room?
Is there like a jungle print?
I'm having trouble figuring out, hold on, let me see.
What counts in my hand?
Hold on one second.
Okay.
Okay, I'll show you the Roy J commercial.
This is the Schweppes commercial.
You believe this is a real commercial in the 80s?
Does anyone remember this commercial from the 80s?
It is called the Speedy Disco and Weird Prisoner.
Guess he dressed like a prisoner.
I mean, now it's in any more pajamas.
I mean, it's like the most strange,
I mean, everyone would remember this character.
Yeah, okay, so one second.
All right, we'll take a look at it.
Shweb's commercial. Oh shit. And uh, oh yeah, you like my I sit back with my neon signs back up
I got that from a spunky. Thank you
Spunky got that for me. Um spunky got that for me a little while ago. It's pretty cool though. Okay. I think it's up
Okay, ready? Here we go. My volume all the way up. Okay. Got it. No, I can't hear anything. Hold on
Here we go. Okay, perfect
I'm relaxed. They don't know the secret. I tell them but they're weird. I'll tell you instead
the secret is sparkling drinks from you know who
there is that okay how i do how is that do you like i mean i'm gonna see his
comedy i mean it's terrible but here i guess i have to search for roi j here's
his comedy tell me if you if you think this is real
hello television land
There's some weird people about her.
Cal stan weird people.
Sliver hither.
In a wine bar last night.
Everyone was whining.
They were all educated and eating.
And they graduated to drinking.
There was this chick at the end of the bar.
She said sliver hither man.
I slithered.
Doing it tomorrow.
I said hey babe, slithered.
She said I guess I'll have champagne.
I said guess again.
We got up close.
I wouldn't say this girl was ugly.
She had a nose like a blind couple of scum.
She was weird.
We went for a meal.
The steak was that tough.
It offered me out in the car park.
The bill came to 200 pounds.
I want to let her in.
She was wild.
Weird.
I thought impress this chick, Jay.
Impress her.
So I flicked a tic-tac.
It wasn't my night.
Went right up a nose.
See, okay.
First of all, that's like too edgy for the 80s.
What a joke.
If that's a little bit too edgy for the 80s,
like doing jokes about cocaine,
he also does jokes about, like,
rastafarians and smoking blunders.
I mean, so that's like not, like,
comedy that would be in the 80s on like a show?
I don't know, does that make sense?
But second of all, if you look at it,
if you don't understand how AI looks when it's rendered,
to make these pretty much,
they made a bunch of fake appearances,
but it's like, you can see his eyes are off
and then he has these gloves
because it makes it easier for the AI
to calculate the number of fingers or something like that.
It is weird. It's just weird. I mean, it's like they're not gonna make jokes about snorting a tic-tac in a club and stuff
I mean, that's just like because these are like British shows that were like on prime time kind of like there wasn't like late-night shows
It was like so it was kind of like a little bit too edgy. I think for that, especially I don't know
Guys you know I have my gong to my gongs up
My gong isn't it weird weird man, and why are they doing it? I think it's just people
So those are both gifts, those are both cool gifts, huh?
Okay, oh, there's Lola, hi Lola.
Weird, man.
And he's like, and then it's like,
and then no comic had, like, okay, first of all,
he's also British or Scottish or something,
but he's, or Norwegian, I guess,
but he has like a, he sounds like Robin Williams
and Jim Carrey half the time, and it's like,
and I don't know, it's just weird.
I think it's funny, I think that it's like
something that they put out there.
The fool people but also the fuck with people. It's like the Mandela effect stuff, too
Like, you know Mandela effect how they're like, oh my gosh in the original Snow White. She doesn't say
Mirror mirror on the wall. She says
Magic mirror upon my wall or something like that and then everyone remembers mirror mirror on the wall
But no one remembers and so the any if you go to the original movie yet does a magic mirror on the wall
And that's always like, you know, I'm not arguable, but
There's it's been parodied and referenced a million times as as the wrong thing
So that's why we remember a different thing. So sometimes that as for Baron stain Baron Stein
Hey, you say tomato I say tomorrow. I was like, you can really tell if it was an A or an E or how they pronounced it
You know, if you're Jewish, I guess you'll say Stein. I mean, it's like and I don't know
It makes I don't even know if they were Jewish Stan and Jan Bernstein, you know, there was there
There were a couple that wrote those books. I used to love Bernstein Bears
Did it some really cool?
Cool books and you know, I know there's a lot of them here. There's I had pretty tight like 50 or 100. Hello. Hello. Hi
Oh, who's GL who's GL?
GI
Um, I don't see them.
Um, I don't know.
So that, my gosh, you know, you know, this is terrible.
Is that he-man person?
I mean, it's like, I knew he-man was like just a big two-face,
a big two-face every time, because I'd catch her or whatever.
It's supposedly a woman.
It probably looks like a man, but I'm just saying,
people are like, oh, why is he attacking people?
You should hear what this person says about me
in chats and stuff like that.
Oh, this animal abuser, he set up a website
to stalk people.
I mean, that sounds like something
Alexander Mayer's would say.
I mean, it's like, I mean, really, I mean, it's like.
Hey man, let's take your medication please and stop the game my name out of your mouth
I mean you're blocked. You're not coming back. I kept modding you a hundred times. I'm so stupid
I don't know why I'm so stupid. I must have like either like the worst memory or the best heart
I mean, it's like there's something
There's a charisma. I it's terrible. It's terrible like
You know, it's one thing if you can you're allowed to go anywhere you want like you can go you can go to any chat
You want and stuff like that, but I and the people are saying why are you picking up?
It's because I had them modded and then then they're they were like, you know, they would go like this
There we go in the chat. They would go
Something like this, but they put my uh
My my nightbot links they would go like this and they would go like this and so you guys do that too, you know, maybe I'll
You might just get modded, but please but please just mean it. I mean, it's like I don't know why this person was doing this and then
goes around and
Plus this person now they've been doxed and it's like and they're lucky that Tommy James didn't put their picture up
But he was like, oh, hey, man's nice. Hey, man's cool. They're a chatter
He means not nice or cool. Okay?
Yeah, it's very cringe.
He-Man.
Get a life.
I mean, it's like, gee, so many people is like, it seems like their existence is like
hating me.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it's all I see, I see them do.
I mean, it's like, they're just, and it's like, I'm supposedly talking about everybody
all the time.
I react.
Maybe they say they're reacting, but it's like, no, I'll go, I can play like a random
episode of, you know.
Beat his titties and you can find them bitching about me in any given time
Wait, let's go to rumble and see if I can find anything. I mean and say they're just bullies. They're so mean and
It's what what's this stuff about? I mean, I say, I I don't know like
They're making fun of a not not her but it was somebody else is making fun of pebs
I know our people have they were on her show too. They're like, oh my god. Look how fat it's like
First of all, she's not she's not that and it's like second of all like why are you why is it like such a?
Anybody can be any side. I mean it's like you know people have different I mean we're not we're not all like cookie cutter people
Like why does it matter what size that somebody I don't understand, but are they trying to date? She's already has a boyfriend
I mean it's not like you know
She's trying to impress anybody, but anyway
I think it's kind of weird. It's kind of like you know, there's a little bit of bullying I think
But let's see it. Let's watch some shrimp cake
Remember I showed I showed this trip kicks thumbnail once of like, you know, Kate's picture and then that that person who's also an awful awful person
I think go Asia demons name by the way
Person PURS away. They're like
Oh my god, he was so upset that he showed a thumbnail of your picture, of a decay.
It doesn't matter that it was a thumbnail, I mean, that's all I could find.
I have handy.
It doesn't look like that gorgeous, like, succubus creature in the clouds right there,
nor does she look like a turtle, nor does she look like, you know, Darcy from 90 Day Fiance,
which is like her AI photo, right?
And she's like, she says, I misuse AI.
That is a crime to change your picture so much
from with AI, I think.
I mean, jeez, I'm presented like, oh, this
is just my picture.
We know you look like an ogre.
You don't look like Jennifer Lopez 10 years ago, OK?
We get it, OK?
But anyway, I digress.
OK, so let me see the trick here.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I get so nasty sometimes, but you just
Got to let it roll off my back, I guess, but I'm not a duck
Disabilitated with some certain quackers. Okay black ass Dave gets attacked in New York City
Maces and runs away. It sounds good. Who's black ass Dave?
Let's watch this one. Has anybody heard of black ass Dave? I think I agree. He man is a creep, right?
I mean, it's like guys. I mean, I mean, they're obvious. I mean, they're just like
What's wrong with them? They're just I think they're just they're just like they're they're headed so far
Abita and Sam and his ass. They're basically they're their next child
Okay, I'm second. Here we go. You see this on the screen. Yeah, okay
back up
What you want to do, huh? What we done? Oh, we done we're doing aerobics
we're doing umbrella robics now we're doing umbrella robics now uh we're doing umbrella
robics now we're doing umbrella you're doing umbrella in my face you feel tough about that
bro you said umbrella in my face bro the fuck up my face oh oh
is that even is he black
He's running. Why is he running away? I guess he was a maced guy or someone got maced
How much longer miss? I missed three trains waiting for you
I gotta get home to my kids. You don't care about my kids now
They got no kids your own you evil bitch. Oh my god. Fuck you
Literally you're evil bro. You're an evil person, bro. You're fucking evil person, dude
You're an evil person, dude
You are
I did nothing to nobody, but you stopping me.
You're a little evil people, bro.
You're a little evil people.
You got into a fight.
You're taking 40 minutes to write a ticket, bro.
That's all IPT people do is clown.
You're an ecstatic excuse for a cop.
You're a fucking clown, dude.
You're an ecstatic-
You're a fucking dumb clown.
You're a stupid clown, dude.
Oh, look at it all rest up.
Bro, I'm trying to get my streaming phone back on, bro.
That's it.
what's that noise uh i'm a swanger miss miss all right i'm gonna i'll get the tickets since
y'all already got my id can i get my id can i get my id just mail on the ticket can i get my id
can i get my id and i'll get the tickets they're ready to my name right can i get my id no
knock i want my id now to fucking aid am i detained okay two tickets two tickets for playing music
You guys are awesome, man.
Yeah.
He was.
You guys are awesome, dude.
I'm sorry I left.
I was like, sorry.
I thought it was okay to leave.
How was ghost?
It was great.
You okay?
You're making me miss my trains, you fucking bitch.
Fuck you and your family, Ridley.
Carol, that's if you died in a fire tonight.
Fuck you and your family, you fucking stupid whore.
Fuck you too.
Don't look at me you faggot fuck you kill yourself faggot fuck you and your family
Literally you guys won't me a ticket over this non-show look look what I do to these tickets fucking the idiots
Look what I do to these tickets. I mean literally no don't touch me nigga
Look what I do your fucking dumb dumb shit tickets nigga look what I do your stupid ass tickets fuck you and your dog shit shit
Fuck you fuck you
I'm leaving. I'm leaving
What should we come back
Come back for what? I'm leaving.
I'm going to rock, bro.
I don't want to hear it.
I went into...
I went five of you guys out right now.
Who's you guys?
Five of you motherfuckers at the house.
It's just me, nigga. You're talking to just me.
Who's you guys?
He's black. He's black.
I'm one person, bro.
What are you talking about, nigga?
You sound retarded, dude.
No, but you went on chat and said,
Fuck Black Dave, right or wrong?
Nigga, stop trying to spin.
Did you or did you not say that?
So why are you stream sniping me nigga?
Why the fuck did you pull up on me?
Weirdo?
It's a dirty ass weed.
Hey, where the fuck did you go?
Did you go stream snip doozy nigga?
Doozy.
Yeah, doozy.
Dude, I'm gonna have you dressed.
Did you or did you not say fuck Black Day?
I'm gonna have your ass dressed.
Right.
This is a who you know scenario.
I'm asking you a question.
No, stop spinning, bro.
Did you or did you not say fuck Black Dave?
I'm going to make sure you go.
Did you or did you not say that?
If we were in a conflict zone, this conversation wouldn't even
be played now.
Did you or did you not say that?
The only reason you're doing this is that you're not
safe enough to fuck the camera, nigga.
Nigga, I saw you say that.
And I was like, yo, he a fake ass nigga when I said that.
I'm going to say fuck you right now.
You didn't chat.
You can say fuck me. Oh, you know, you're still speaking on me. You fuck. I'm saying is that the brother from Everybody Loves Raymond
You came to you came to follow me where that's nigga
You're in the yo, you're gonna have a fucking nightmare. Did you or did you not say fuck black Dave, bro?
Yes, or no, is it? I'm saying fuck you now. No, no, but did you fuck you now? Okay, cool
But I'm pressing you cuz I'm saying fuck you now. Oh, yeah, so fuck you too. Fuck. Yes
But did you did you not say that
Okay, you don't remember, so you're just a psychotic hater with low IQ and so fuck you too with your dirty ass sweet nigga?
Fuck yeah, get crazy nigga. Get crazy nigga. Get crazy nigga. Get crazy nigga. You know, it's crazy nigga
That's crazy nigga. Fuck you and your family nigga. Get crazy nigga. Get crazy bitch. Get crazy bitch. Come on
Come on nigga. Come on. Come on. That's assault cuz I knocked your weed out your hand is the salt
I knocked your weed out your hand is the salt nigga roll that dirty ass weed up roll it up roll it up cuz
Don't go sticky fuck you nigga. Don't don't leech off scrubs and so you finger up
Myself I don't need you. I don't need you. I don't need scrubs. I don't need so
Stop never shim snipe me again in your life. All right, you weirdo, huh?
So do it draft me nigga in the imaginary war that you'll never have draft me. Fuck you
I you just I you should have never said fuck black Dave in kick fuck fuck black
Dave right now of course nigga now fuck you look at your shit look at your
fucking crotch look at your crotch look at your crotch you should snort that you
crackhead you should snort that bitch why would you ever stream tonight me in
your life
So I haven't seen these I guess let me see
Who's that? Oh God. Okay. Let's see
Mmm, I didn't see the he may see yeah, he made somebody
Okay, okay, what is it? I mean look at three months ago. It's like like he had a post. I don't hear a lot chicken
And he gets whooped by Darius IRL
part 3
Always has
I know
Float up all your girlfriend's garbage in the stuff room.
She's just an old woman.
Dude, I've already cleaned up all my trash.
Okay, but I'm cleaning out your girlfriend's stuff.
And it's on your computer.
Yeah, yeah, I'll give you another TV, man.
Another TV, I didn't get to hear what you were telling me about, man.
You see, he's coming over here telling us what to do.
I'm asking you to help move your trash out of the house.
We had a new house, dude, man.
It looks like he's kind of looked down on us and shit.
Want to see me Sandman and Bronze and Fita?
Yeah, that was real quick, though.
Oh, yeah, we're coming, man.
Aw, that ain't too bad.
You want it? I heard the
insides kind of. Ew. Yeah.
You know, she's um you know,
that's not that should be a
or maybe this is I don't like
this. I don't know. I don't
know, man. I can make a call
if you guys want anything.
Oh, those are those are some of the parties man, we would have really partied up in this
Oh
Yeah, I told you
I didn't buy that one
Yeah, I'm giving away all the appliances, man. Come start pulling it out right now, dude.
Oh boy!
I think there's some copper in the walls, man. We should start shipping this bitch.
I still live here, so you guys are my guests, you know?
Yep, this is typical right here. It's cheap pressed board. Yeah, that's broken. I'm lucky. I found that I was gonna fix it for them
But then yeah
What is this
Let's not gay, you guys gay.
I don't know, I'm good man.
That's him, not me.
Alright, alright.
Now I look like an angry YNCA guy.
Yeah dude, this is, I don't even believe this.
Yeah, you know, what's up with this guy?
I know, you're barely going down the fucking inch dude.
What the fuck?
What happened?
You barely on an inch on this box
Dude the furry cosplays dude, what is Pokemon?
You're either miles or murders of pedophiles well, okay
Disclosure, I mean gosh, what it means Jesus. There's a costume to sit. Okay, so there's I wouldn't talk about this disclosures thing
I'm fine something
So I'll share a quick video about it because I had INX on last night and you know
we're interested in like branching out into like you know actually talking about cool things rather than all the drama all the time and so
I found, let me see if I can find this one
Cool pinning, here we go, here it goes. Okay. Hi Lola. Hi, baby. Okay. Is this the right one?
Okay, it should say
Okay, I hit it in more.
Okay, it must be on the other channel.
Okay, it's called Shaking My Head.
Here we go.
So this is about the disclosure stuff,
but in my opinion, all the disclosure stuff
is like Project Bluebeam kinda,
which is like, basically it's all fake.
It's all to distract from something else.
But I'll let you be the judge of that.
Let me see, disclosure, disclosure, disclosure.
Oh, here it is, I found it, okay.
Tell me what you think. We'll watch this together. This is a short short clip. I think you like it
Okay, I'll look for that next. I'll look for that next. Okay. One second. Just give me a second
I'm gonna watch this first. It is time for us to adopt a new company brand to encompass everything that we do
To reflect who we are and what we hope to build. I am proud to announce that starting today
Our company is now
I could not have written Ready Player One if I had not grown up on a study diet of
Steven Spielberg movies. It would have been a different story or I might not have written it
at all. His work is woven into the fabric of my life. Everybody I think who dreams of making
movies, dreams of getting to work with him, it's the dream come true.
I wanna tell you about the brand new Mr. Beast Lab hybrids.
These are collectible action figures
that you can take apart, mix and match,
and make your very own unique beast.
Some of these hybrids are even super rare,
like this Golden Dragon or this 1 in 1,000 Hypercrow.
You just combined the rare as hybrids.
Don't sell it on eBay.
And with our brand new mega pack,
look how many pieces you can start your collection with.
Bro, it just keeps going.
Mr. Beast Lab hybrids.
Wherever you buy toys, these bad boys are available.
Are all your phony economic crisis as-as-as is being exposed?
Is the price of gold defying all your attempts to fix it?
Isn't killing the Gulf of Mexico and poisoning millions of people
reducing the population fast enough for you?
War, famine, and GM food not getting it done either?
No?
Well, don't give up!
Get disclosure!
You'll be able to unite mankind with a phony problem and enslave them with one world government and taxes.
Yes. Disclosure. Your one-stop shop for full spectrum dominance.
But wait, there's more. Sign up for disclosure today and you'll get problem, reaction, solution, absolutely free.
That's right. Absolutely free. Act now to be entered into our fabulous propaganda prize draw.
Disclosure. Our surveys show that 9 out of 10 world leaders prefer it.
Disclosure. Cleansing the minds of the unwashed masses with a tantalizing, terrifying, taxable new reality.
I'm only going to say this three times, Disclosure!
Disclosure!
Aliens may or may not be real. Your home may be at risk from those possible aliens.
No major credit cards accepted because there is only one currency after a one-world government.
Prepare to die screaming probably. Disclosure is compatible with Project Bluebeam. Do not employ critical thinking.
A future that Ernest Klein, the writer of the book, envisioned.
I was very careful with Ernie collaborating with me every step of the way to be able to find the
movie narrative inside this dense forest of Ernie's profound imagination.
The Oasis being the ultimate toy box with all the toys in the world and then playing that with
one of the greatest filmmakers of all time. It results in just amazing action and such a fun
adventure. Ernie's climb is such a visionary and I think has seen the future before any of us
here's the so this this clothes is going pretty good huh see this clothes this clothes is getting
pretty good here we go to the most of the short one let's see we kind of already did okay let's
watch this one daughter running this charity they're just trying to help vulnerable families
in one direction boys really like the message believe in magic when it blowballs it's just magical
and then out of the blue
I just had a hunch that jeans full of
They are not being open about how that charity money is being used. It's literally trending number one. Can you believe it?
Well, we haven't seen ET yet
Some people think that day is coming soon. The White House is getting ready to roll one out and they want some advice
There's a lot of speculation, I'm hearing it from people inside the administration,
that the Trump administration is indeed soliciting advice about how to tell the public that we're not alone.
There was some luxury villa in Disneyland.
The story doesn't add up.
I just wanted to get to the truth.
Bosses have all been killed part after part.
It's too shocking to believe.
Himea Gowlett, she wasn't safe.
This was the time to speak to the police.
There are consultations taking place with spiritual leaders.
I'm now able to confirm that.
Well, we still...
Haven't seen everything, but UFO experts say the good stuff is coming if people keep pushing
It was all over social media horrendous. What was there for me to lie about?
We were going to find out the truth
If people keep the pressure on, the records will come out more of them and they will be
shocking some of them.
David Grush tested by two bodies, non-human intelligence bodies.
So there's got to be autopsies, there's got to be photographs and footage.
No.
We don't want to see an alien body just for the fun of it.
We need to know what they're capable of.
Today this was an official Guinness World Records attempt for largest aerial display
It's so big that it's like, I mean, we need to be able to, like, organize stuff.
It's the fact that this technology does stuff that we can't do.
And if we can't figure out what it is, or what it wants, or what it's being used for,
that keeps me up at night in the idea that we're behind the power curtain.
Brett Feddersen is a former White House National Security Council director of aviation security,
and this is Feddersen's first interview since the age of disclosure.
Brett, you mentioned that this keeps you up at night.
Tell us why.
Thanks for having me on, Jesse.
The reason it does is twofold.
One is the fact that this type of technology is not man-made.
It's nothing that we can build or have built or are using out there.
And the fact that we're seeing it so presently on a regular basis globally makes it a national
security threat.
Additionally, the fact that it is out in our airspace and all around as travel is moving
that it is a flight safety issue as well and it's something that needs to be continued,
be pressed, needs to be addressed and tracked.
What do you think you're going to see like commercial airlines crash into UFOs?
You know, surprisingly, there's been a large uptick in commercial airline pilots reporting
UAPs on a daily basis is what the FBI and the FAA are telling us.
I am much more inclined now than I was for to make close encounters.
To really believe that we're not the only intelligent civilization in the universe.
What did you steal?
Secrets.
People have a right to know the truth.
This is a story about us. All of us.
Good morning Kansas City.
Okay, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second, hold
put people in fantasies and things like that?
I mean, they're acting like they know something
and that they're going to disclose and stuff.
The disclosure's not that they're aliens,
it's that the humans are the aliens.
That's the disclosure, I mean.
But I won't get too far into it.
I'm frightened, I'm frightened out of my wits.
You don't need to be, you have someone else.
Daniel Keller.
Who is this?
Do not go back to the house.
They found you, I don't know who you are,
but they're gonna kill you.
The human race cannot accept what we know.
One shot is what it's all about.
The deer has to be taken with one shot.
Blessed is the kingdom of the Father,
and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
What's with the creepy deer and leave the world behind?
Netflix's latest hit movie Leave the World Behind is defined by a disconcerting deluge
of unsettling imagery, but nothing is quite as creepy as the deer that seemed to stalk
the main characters.
Netflix's version makes some big changes to the book that Leave the World Behind is based
on, but many of the most notable elements from the novel carry over to the film adaptation.
The disturbing behavior of the deer is one such element that translates directly from
page to screen. Throughout the course of the movie's terrifying events, the deer that
approached the Scots property, and the surrounding area change in both numbers and attitude,
starting with a doe and fawn innocently walking in the garden.
Okay, you hear that the dough and so so this is like a this is like a pedophilia kind of sigh up
If you can pick up on it, that's what the deer stuff is all about. There's also it's also, you know
So like things like get out
He hits the deer and stuff's a bad omen the deer hunter
Then they had this leave the world behind with the deer going crazy and stuff and then it's it's a it's a it's like a code
but
you come up with your own conclusion.
You've got to listen to me.
You want to stay down here and die?
Here we are.
We're looking at the first 9-11 event.
When 9-11 happened itself and we see Bush in the classroom
and him with the teacher.
And we've, of course, seen the same sort of imagery
in I Pet Goat 2 where the pet goat, like Bush was reading
the pet goat to the children.
Here we have the second one.
and associated with it is a second 9-11 attack, a 9-11 style attack, false flag attack, only this
time much larger with much more devastating effects to the United States. You've got to listen to me.
You want to stay down here and die. And what we're seeing over and over again is a repeated theme.
The theme is that there is a solar eclipse followed by a full moon where a solar eclipse followed by a buck moon
Which is also called a stag moon
okay
for obvious reasons and then and so we have
this
theme that these the solar eclipse followed by the buck moon is
very closely associated with a very devastating change or turn in world
affairs, an attack, a catastrophe followed by major events, something like this.
Leave the world behind's ambiguous ending left many questions unanswered, and the mystery
surrounding the deer was one of the most vexing.
What the deer symbolize and leave the world behind?
The behavior of the deer was partially explained by a blink and you'll miss it news report
heard over the radio in Clay's car.
An environmental disaster in the south caused by the cyber attack had impacted animal migration
patterns.
While the nature of the disaster is left-baked, it is also the explanation for the arrival
Apart from acting is another symptom of the cyber attack at the heart of leave the world behind.
The deer act is a powerful symbol. The increasing number and hostility of the deer is a direct
parallel to the fear and mistrust that infects each of the characters as the normalcy of the world
around them slowly erodes. We need to stop it. Anyway, we can. What am I doing? What am I doing?
We are interrupting our coverage.
How will disclosure change us?
I believe for the better.
It will remind us of our capacity for empathy.
And that there is something bigger out there than just ourselves.
Since the stigma has been broken, mainly because of movies like The Age of Disclosure,
pilots both in the military and in the commercial sector are coming forward with what they're seeing.
Aren't as afraid to actually say, I've seen something that's not a drone,
it's not another flight object, it's something we don't understand.
And when we see these, describe the level of technological superiority.
Yeah, so we've been seeing these obviously for decades, you know, the idea that the agent's
closure came was that Dan Farah was able to get us to 34 senior officials to trust him
and break our silence about a 80-year cover-up.
Well, the hidden agenda becomes ever more obvious in the mainstream media.
I only hope that people out there will start to wake up to exactly what's going on.
and how it reflects the absolute truth that is the Bible and prophecy.
But this commercial, I'm going to show you, for example, here for Jagermeister.
Yeah, I mean, it's Hunter, it's a master hunter.
But I'm saying, like, thinking about how is it like the kind of the
deer head iconic of like the animal that's like, OK, to be shot.
And they're beautiful.
And you can mount their heads on the wall and stuff like that.
And and, you know.
And it's not selective bias. I'm saying I mean there there's these symbols are put there especially corporate symbols
Which is like basically a sigil is like a magical sigil because it's actually like a design to be mass-produced and
To work on a subconscious level. I mean, yeah, oh it means hunter
You know people just hunt deer and there's like, you know, so we master hunter or whatever my sir Jager Meister, so
Hi little nor kisses, okay
Look and look at
It says BKG. Is that me? Oh my god. Oh my god. I'm so screwed. What are you? What are you a German expert now?
I think that is
It's not to convince anything. I don't have here. Well, I have my own view of it
I'm explaining my view of it. You can take whatever you want from it
This is showing you things in the media that are shown to everybody. I think they're not shown to you for
Randomness for entertainment. It's always with the purpose
Okay, you see the four wolves around the deer. Okay
We get this scene that I just showed you where the whisperer comes in gives him the vision
And he looks and we clearly in the vision
Have depicted
A an annular eclipse or an eclipse at least. Okay, it's actually a pretty cool way to depict it
But it you know, it looks that way, but if you look I mean
I don't know would actually look that way if you had a big fire outside
You wouldn't have the darkened center that was done by the producers of the film
certainly, okay, and then I mean the whole thing is CGI or whatever it is. It's it's just
computer graphics
Okay, they didn't have a real fire outside. So so he's gonna go over to this and we see of course the buck
That's enough the buck the stag. Oh, okay, and the stag is burning
Again, it's not the eclipse that is the catastrophe doesn't look like the eclipse is what paves the way for
This what's really burning
Is that so below buck moon?
But even still, without the Bible and the Holy Spirit and the roadmap of prophecy that we've been given, written for thousands of years, then it wouldn't be obvious.
So we have God to thank for that.
This is about the mark of the beast.
And let's go through this commercial together.
So it's going into a worldly club.
You know, this all stems from him being part of the world, part of worldliness at this party.
He sees up these stairs some antlers, a shadow actually of some antlers.
So it's kind of there but it's not really there because when someone walks past it's gone again.
So you see the hintness being made that this is actually potentially part of the spirit realm.
This is a shadow, a temporary shadow that he gets tempted by, allured by.
Right
How did you get in here my god? That's not important now listen carefully
You have to watch Midnight Spank a new block of late night shows on G4 why because I can make everyone you've ever loved
Disappear David disappear forever
Oh
What?
Now as you can see this creature is a stag that's being shown he's walk gonna walk up the stairs towards it
Now the stag god ties to Nimrod and the hunter
I used to say to myself wouldn't it be wonderful if all of this turned out to be true
I'm now thinking wouldn't it be wonderful for people to know all of this is true. Oh my god
about UAPs and non-human intelligent life.
When we're seeing these, we're seeing very bright orbs, very bright.
objects that are meeting some energy, but they're not showing propulsion.
They're instantaneously taking off into different directions. Again,
things that physics has inhibited us from being able to do as humans.
We're continuing to see that type of technology proliferate.
It's interesting to note that several of the astronauts in several of the earlier days
where fighter pilots were reporting them during World War II,
this same type of descriptions are exactly what we're seeing.
now in the files and the videos to be released. Well then it absolutely is a national security
threat and it does seem, according to the reporting, that this administration's having
discussions about how to break this to the American people.
equivalent to Baphomet, The Ox, Sanunos, Saturnus, The Beast, The Bull, Baal, all of those things together are types and shadows of the same thing.
But ultimately, this is representing Nimrod.
Now, you notice how the music starts to change, everything goes in slow motion. This is hinting at him almost going through the veil into a different dimension.
And he walks through these doors.
The first thing you see, of course, are these antlers or these horns,
just like going into a temple of Bar, a temple of Saturnus,
basically the devil, the red bull.
And he's walking through into this chamber.
You get it?
Jesus said, if they say he's out there in the secret chambers, do not go out there.
And when that day comes, oh my God, that's going to be historic.
Well, Brett, thank you so much for talking to us and coming forward, and we wish you the best.
It looks like we're all on this journey together.
When he looks up, you can see that it's part of a dome.
You see that it's a dome roof.
Now, the dome is female or feminine symbolism.
You then look at the word matrix and womb, and that they do, in fact, link together.
So essentially, you can say that he is now walking into the womb or the matrix.
And to top it off, this is actually called an oculus.
It's what they call it in the architecture the the structure of that would be referred to in these buildings in these old buildings as an
Oculus which is like a portal or a gate
Again, in regards to that female symbolism, we've got the moon being shown through this
oculus and the moon has got connotations towards the female, towards Diana, the moon goddess.
So this is Luciferian propaganda.
This is representing Lucifer, the light bearer.
the moon being the light bearer of the sun and this is what they're using it for
is all a direct inversion of Jesus Christ in many many ways so this is a
promotion of the mother goddess which we flick to here which is the the Greek
Artemis equivalent of the Roman Diana moon goddess
We just wanted to make you aware that we are getting a special word from the president as we continue to watch this operation to retrieve the four astronauts
President Trump saying congratulations to the great and very talented crew of Artemis 2
The entire trip was spectacular. The landing was perfect and as president of the United States
I could not be more proud and of course the hunter huntress
Which she's often depicted with a bow and arrow
It's a dome, right there to the arena.
Uh, the pouring the water, like the age of Aquarius.
But you see, you've got the moon there, and then you've got Apollo the Sun God.
So it's the sun and moon, it's all the same, uh, pagan rituals.
So this is, this is what this is, a Luciferian pagan ritual with two pillars, and Apollo the Sun God.
ABBA, oh my god!
I'm just blowing your mind, huh?
And this horned God is actually another way of showing the uterus.
So you see how that this, again, is a reference to the matrix or the womb.
And this chair right here, sitting there ready for this guy who's been tempted in,
like the Bible says, this temptation that comes upon the whole world,
it's not forced, it's a temptation to take the mark of the beast.
Look, it's completely his choice.
And that I mean so that is what this is. This is the devil. This is the mark of the beast
It's the red devil. It's the red bull right behind him. Hey, well I'll play Call of Duty want to overpay for some pizza
I guess
Come on dudes get slices and sticks for me $6.99. I get Call of Duty black ops seven rewards
Deal dear. What's your gamer tag? I'm deal dear gamer, too
Son of a took deal dear gamer. Yeah
Level up with slices and sticks in Call of Duty Black Ops 7 in-game rewards.
Little Caesars is the real deal.
Pizza, pizza.
Little Caesars drops a hilarious new spot, starring NFL star George Kittle.
And this one immediately grabs attention.
The commercial opens with pure chaos.
Kittle bursts in riding the now iconic Deal Deer,
smashing through the scene with dramatic Game Day energy.
The Talking Deer delivers one mission.
Bring fans the ultimate value deal the offer two large pizzas for just 499 each when ordering online
simple loud
Legendary value
Visually the ad leans into fast-paced comedy
Exaggerated action and playful mascot energy blending sports hype with little Caesar's trademark humor
It's over the top ridiculous in the best way and laser focused on one message
Great pizza great price
Real deal which leaves viewers thinking one thing football nights and pizza just got even better
Will you buy the lie? Will you buy the lie of self-assention?
Will you buy the lie of completely and utterly rejecting Christ with no return?
I mean this is what and you see through this is another way of showing self-assention
They're taking this mark this electronic mark
All right Tom your thoughts. Yeah, well, um
step aside who put these in Tom only Duracell has power boosting ingredients
why winners like Tom here only run on Duracell Tom are you okay why does
everyone keep asking me that since the roast I got to go grunks down again look
at that flashes of the mother goddess Lucifer and and Tamus the raging bull
For 30 years, these thrill-seekers have been tempting fate, braving this wild ride.
In just a few months ago, we saw an epic race for the PBR teams title.
Today it's a dawn of a new day. PBRs unleash the beast.
You know, this is a permanent final rejection of Christ, and this is sealing the deal, sealing the fate, which is the agenda of the enemy to lead your soul to hell.
That is all that this is showing.
You're taking the mark of the raging bull, of the opposite and inversion of Christ, the mark of evil being sealed by hell.
So then we go through this animation and you see that this reference as we've seen a few times like to this being like a game of level up of self ascension, basically, so again, as I said, this is all a reference to Nimrod, the hunter.
buying the lie, just like in the Garden of Eden, that you shall be as God.
There's actually subliminals, look at this, before he takes on what you'd call the boss.
Live forever, there's one of them.
Look at these little subliminals they add in that last for less than a fraction of a millisecond.
One frame. Live forever.
This is the individual game.
The most precious award in this world.
where a cowboy gets their name etched in history.
Every day I thank God that I can come and compete
in a situation like this.
This is the greatest day ever.
So that's part of what this is showing.
You know, this counterfeit eternal life of Lucifer.
This counterfeit lie that people think they can live forever
through this self-ascension.
So all of these representing like taking on the boss or the beast.
But it's all a Hegelian dialect taking on death, you know
ascending to the next stage in human evolution.
But all of this follows the principles in a counterfeit way of when lambs become lions,
when deers become stags, when mice become men.
This is following a counterfeit version of that.
When we know that the only way to truly overcome the power of death and sin and the devil
is to humble yourself like a child and ask the Messiah to forgive you and so that you might
find your identity in him through humility.
It's also the dawn of a new day on a new network on Paramount Plus.
Every ride counts, not only for these riders, but for the best bulls in the world.
So he's taking on the wolf there again like this whole game and as this is showing him
growing stronger and stronger ascending up and up you see these flashes of the
And all these references to the womb and the matrix and how this is the mark of the beat.
I mean, look, essentially what this is actually doing is tattooing them on a cellular level with,
when you listen to the way it's being tattooed and the sounds that are being played with this, listen.
So you hear that it's all electronic, so it's already showing you that this is in some way
A transhuman this is in some way electronic combining with man and the matrix the mark of the matrix.
From the imagination comes the story of a man.
Come on boy. Let's go grass is waiting for you with the mind of a child. Yeah cyborg man
He came to see me cyborg man comments, right? Yeah cyborg man
And the doctor virtual reality holds a key to the evolution of the human mind with a vision of the future
I have a game in my house that you might like to play was like that
Yeah, okay
Really bad
I have different games.
I even have one that could help make you smarter.
Now, Job Smith is about to enter the world of virtual reality.
It's gonna hit me!
No, no, no, just relax.
It's gonna be like being up there with the stars, Job.
They're going to another planet.
His mind is like a clean, hungry sponge.
I just graduated to the next level, Job.
You're not the one woman. You've certainly changed. I didn't know how you did it, but I approve
It's all black. That's been in less than two hours
A world where the normal course of events can suddenly turn
Inside out, I can realize Dr. Angelo and my intelligence has surpassed yours.
The imaginary becomes real.
Trying to get inside my head, Joe.
You can't hide anything from me, Dr. Angelo.
And reality...
We have no idea what he's gonna do.
...is all in your mind.
And this is making him one with The Beast.
So, facing the giant in a counterfeit way.
This is impossible without the real Christ.
This is all part of a lie.
This is a trick to tickle the itching ears of egomania in people.
Of self-love, if not you, then who?
You see how this is all tying into everything we're seeing in society, perilous times, everything
you see now is about self-love and self-elevation.
So own it, here we go, you know, now he's gaining strength, it's like, as I said, that
counterfeit of lambs become lions, of deer become stags, own it.
You can do it yourself.
You can build your tower of fable.
So he's become a man, you know, through this, this is what this is showing, with this fleshly matrix music also being added.
Hunt or be hunted, so the hunter, and this also ties into the persecution of those who won't take the mark.
So this is, you know, grasping on that fear, if you don't become a hunter, then you will be hunted.
And this is the great trick, you know, this is very well could be how it all plays out, especially to begin with, you know, the Christians are seen as weak, that those who humble themselves are seen as weak, those that aren't going to join that agenda.
They're seen as weak because the New Age is going to want to get rid of them. There's even quotations about that, that somehow we're holding it all back.
And so the ones that don't follow the pride of this will be seen as the weak ones that need to be hunted.
So hunt or be hunted. Join with the beast or be hunted.
So now he's fully self ascended and he in their eyes and he's now marked by this beast.
Wow. And now apparently that makes him a man.
because he's merged with the beast, he's marked, he's become one of it, he's become
one in the body of the beast. But I tell you what, the real strength doesn't come from
conforming to that, the real strength comes from resisting that.
This is not strength at all. This actually represents, in terms of God's kingdom, judgment and destruction and conforming with that which is unclean and taking a no return ticket to hell.
Today's modern technology aims to improve animal welfare and operational efficiencies.
The 701X livestock management system encompasses a software platform and electronic ear tag
to provide a solution for tracking individual animal and herd level data.
Key features include a digital calving book, interactive map.
offline data entry mode health and gps alerts along with custom reports regarding inventory
performance and more 701x provides you the tools to shape the next generation of ranching and promote
sustainability so hunt or be hunted wow i mean that couldn't be much more blatant could it he
And he goes through a process of self-elevation
under the influence of the spirit of Antichrist and Baal.
And he self ascends to the point where he becomes a real, quote-unquote, real man
through this process.
And then we're reminded at the end, you either hunt or you become the hunted.
And we've looked at this Jägermeister logo before.
and discussed some of what it actually means.
But I want to take that a bit further today and show you how this links to secret societies.
Now, as well as all the occult references we've exposed before with the Jägermeister and its logo,
actually it's pretty interesting looking at this international order of Saint Hubertus.
And you can see how this has very, very close similarities with the Jägermeister logo.
And this International Order of St. Hubertus is a worldwide organisation
and nightly order of hunters and wildlife conservationists
that promotes traditional hunting ethics and practices.
It was founded in 1695.
So you see there already the link between that and hunting and then the Jägermeister logo and the symbol for the Order of Saint Hubertus.
By the way, with these secret societies, we do pray that everyone that we talk about on here will come to know Christ and we hope the best.
We're not to get into anger over anything that we're seeing.
societies that they would come to know the truth and the life and the love of Christ and our Father in heaven.
And I pray for them all.
So you can already see a blatant link there between Jägermeister
and the secret societies and the logo of Jägermeister being very, very similar for good reason because if you actually look on the Jägermeister Wikipedia, for example,
the label on the Jägermeister bottles features a glowing Christian cross seen between the antlers of a stag.
This image is a reference to the two Christian patron saints of Hunters, Saint Hubertus and Saint Eustace.
So, on the Jägermeister Wikipedia, we have a direct reference to Saint Hubertus.
So you can see that that's no coincidence that there are very close similarities between
that order and this logo on the Jägermeister.
Remember what we just watched in the commercial was essentially, hunt or be hunted, promoting
Seeing the wild hunt was thought to presage some catastrophe, such as war or plague, or at best, the death of the one who witnessed it.
People encountering the hunt might also be abducted to the underworld or the Fairy Kingdom, there's a reference to the other side of the Vale and the underworld.
So, this Jägermeister, this German drink...
With all these links to the Hunter in the Bible, you know, it tells us in the Book of Revelation that saints will be persecuted during this time.
Father in heaven, I thank you that you are beyond anything that we can imagine and that your power is above all things in this world.
All plans and schemes of man and the powers and principalities that seek to steal, kill and destroy.
I pray that you would please open up people's hearts and minds to receive the truth in this time
and maybe through these fickle efforts that we do, that you might speak to the heart of
even just one person who might realize that the Bible is the truth, that you are the truth, and that this is the truth.
I might say a 40, 26, lift up your eyes on high and behold who have created these things.
that bringeth out their host by number.
He calleth them all by names, by the greatness of his might,
for that he is strong in power, not one faileth.
This is what's missing this whole time,
and it's been right in front of our faces in the scripture.
This is what God was showing Ezekiel.
The wheels within the wheels are
The belts that surround Earth, NASA calls Van Allen belts.
These are the invisible belts of magnetic energy within the torus.
Everything in motion, everything moving like a fine tune clock.
All the eyes that Ezekiel saw was the stars.
All the stars are created by God. They are the luminaries.
That is what makes up all the eyes that is being spoken of.
What Ezekiel saw was the absolute pure beauty of our home that God created for us.
This is what Satan wants you blinded to.
This is the magnificence that Satan doesn't want you to see.
This is why they mockingly show you that image and game of thrones in other movies.
The wheels within the wheels over the flat plain earth.
They're showing you the truth right in front of your face.
they laugh because you don't understand and you don't see this is the beauty
this is the sheer of the world that God created and he called it how they move
Kavinok the movement of these wheels we see how the Sun and Moon will go spin
here the whole time instead we choose them to the idiot box instead we choose
and we keep amongst ourselves just look up I wanted to say sitting up there
and be comforted by the fact that even the lines are going to be ever-increasing will still
rob this from me. They will never rob from me, my face." It was pretty good. Okay. What are you
talking about? Hockey? Hi! Okay, I need to talk to you, Jadal. Come on up. We need to clear some
step up. Here we go. There we go. There's the link. Okay. Okay. Hi, guys. So, yeah. I love my neon
Oh, I'm getting a message, it's all right.
Booty?
Why aren't you talking to me?
I have a nice booty.
Why are you talking to Booty Goon all the time?
Are you gooning on Booty?
Booty Goon?
Hey, no one's gonna touch my booty.
Better not.
Okay, so, hi Booty Goon.
Okay, let's actually just keep talking about hockey.
Hockey, no, I'm gay.
I'm sorry, it's like hockey means how gay?
How cocky, how gay?
I'm just kidding, just a joke.
Okay.
Oh.
Hold on one second. Oh, we get to you. Let's welcome to the show
Jadon psyche. What's up, dude? How you been? Okay?
That day you gave me your your email address I like I thought I copied and pasted into like an email client
No, I lost it and then I was like I just thought I'd see you later on the
Oh, yeah, I don't even trip on that bro into whatever I'm not even tripping on that
I was just tripping. I just thought that you didn't want to hang out and I was like, dude
I was in the neighborhood
I didn't want to just show up and knock on your door and then be like
Oh, I'm sorry, but you know, Alexander said, well, you know, he didn't go out with a J-dog,
but he met me, so he must be straight, because she's like, yeah.
And you're on her shit list again. Let me see what she say about you. She said you are working
at this drug gang with like me and Amber and like somebody else mailing meth around the country.
Excellent. J-Dog is running meth now. Excellent. Hell yeah. And before we were a call and now what
were we trafficking? We're a drug trafficking gang now. But we're drug trafficking now.
Whenever we're spiritual, you were spiritual trafficking, remember? I graduated, but you know
You also call it to their pedophiles to create a smoke screen away from our drug dealing exit.
Dude, it's just like...
I don't know. I don't know. I mean, it's like, I don't know. She was like, well, she told me, like, before we, we had another falling out, you know, you heard that.
Yeah, yeah. I thought you guys were cool, and then you guys had a falling out, and then you guys were cool again, then I'll find, like, it was so fast, it happened, like, so quick. Same thing with me and her.
I don't even know if I'm cool with her or not.
No, we're not right now. She doesn't, well, she's mad at everybody associated with me, but, you know, she, uh...
I don't know why and it was just sudden, but yeah
She hates me again and like you know now she's in the beach
She wants to be from the beta and go on Sam and and be with back with Tommy James
And I mean oh, she's trying to hang out with the cool kid
She's be trained everybody else who was cool with her from the beginning and you know
Turned her back on everybody that was really really friends with her or try to be friends with her, but
Wow
Is that INX, Karen?
Yes.
Next Tommy, is that Brandon Q?
Is that supposed to be you?
Yeah.
You have hair, though. I know I also
Fucking over my tattoo, and I don't wear like my dress like you know, I've never seen you dress like that
I've never seen you have your shirts open like that. You've always button them up and you know been proper and primped and stuff like
Tell me James. He looks great. I
Brandon looks and
Look at me. I'm like making a weird face. I'm like, oh my god. I'm like going crazy
You know who she has you looking like remember. Have you ever seen Harold and Kumar?
My god, remember the first one, you know the first one the tow truck driver if you if you google
Harold and Kumar tow truck driver
Pull up that picture. That's how she's trying to make me look
No, I know I know but she's trying to make you look dude
You want to know like a big thing that was going on see that too?
That was an idea came in a ball with me
This is what they remade it to look like she was like me and her look like so so like no
Together we'll come and I look at me. I'm like I like melting. I feel like a pretty Kruger dirty and like
We get good times in that picture good good times like that
Yeah, well that goes to show you well, you know her and Tommy are trying to have a baby right now, right?
You know what what then the next year? She's she's attempting to have a baby with Tommy James. Um, I
Don't know how that's gonna go to be honest dude. I really don't
Cause she was like, and she's like, oh, well, you know, she's like, you know, J-Dog, I saw him on Tommy James show and he was talking shit about me and blah, blah, blah, blah.
I wasn't talking shit about you.
I know, no, no, about you, about her.
So I played the episode and I watched it and you didn't even mention her at all.
You just mentioned her a little bit, but after that.
No, because people were asking me about you. They were saying, hey, so you don't kick it was I go
No, and I told him the story of what happened. That was all that happened
It was nothing bad or nothing like oh fuck psyche or fuck this or it was nothing like that
No, I didn't say nothing bad about her
It's a position's pissed at me because I spread this rumor I go wait a minute. Why are you getting upset with me?
I'm not even the one who spread this rumor Tommy's the one who told me
I just ask everybody else or I put it in public because Tommy I told me in confidence I had told
to ask him I go hey um I'm gonna ask other people because you know you know you know drug addicts
and junkies you know they can't do not tell the truth and you know gives a fib a lot so I didn't
really believe him so I asked him again when you know when I saw him sober I said Tommy is it true
that you and Alex are trying to have a baby within the next year?
Oh my god. Yeah, that pick really does look better than be do beat us just a lost cause dude like really no honesty dude
Beato is just
garbage she was oh yeah so she so yeah she started kissing Christine's ass a few
months ago but then like you know she was on the she's on Samans with Christine
and Christine like was like I don't like you Alice because you're not a very good
journalist and you know you know and so can you read the Bible and you're not
you shouldn't read the Bible like I don't know but she doesn't like Christine
anymore but oh I'm calling you a rat dolphin smoke
Rg came in the chat saying to me yesterday. He just had AIDS like that's what they're all they can do is like say AIDS
HIV dirty pdf. I mean, it's like that's all they call me
Oh my god, well, you already know they're just trolls. Do you already know the same thing with dope and smoke dude? He thinks
Dope and smoke is so funny you bro. It's not even funny bro. He's just a troll. He's not even nobody
Don't even sure what let me make sure I see which is the correct guy
Oh, yeah, yeah, no, I know who he is. Okay. Now. I know who that guy is. Yeah, I know he is
Yeah, he's a troll. He's one of the trolls. That's all he is. I know he is
Like next time let me know again
Bring him up because you know he said he now he says I'm a pedophile now
He says I'm a sex peds now. He's calling me this thing. Okay, I understand and he's saying he's like brought me everything to the show
I I used him for cloud and all this kind of shit
Cloud that fool didn't have no is he backstage? Yeah, you want to let him up?
I'll be more than happy to put this nigga in his place
Hey motherfucker!
I don't need a QA, you fucking pedophile motherfucker!
Hey, what's up, you bitch?
Hey, what did you say that was a fucking...
What the fuck are you nagging at?
You're a pussy nigga!
Hey, you're a pussy nigga!
Turn your camera on!
I'm gonna pussy you!
Turn it on!
Turn it on, bitch!
Fuckin' pedophile motherfucker. Come on, you make psyche by the way.
You made people. Nigga, nobody made you.
Nobody made you. Nobody made you.
You didn't make anybody, bro. You can't even make yourself, bro.
You didn't even make yourself. You can't make, you can't even make a bed, bro.
You can't even make a fucking bed, nigga.
Look, and then you got, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, that's psyche.
Oh, you're in your car? What do you got? A little Ford Focus?
Yeah.
Yeah
Give me your address
Take my job
You have no clue about me, but I know you. I know you
Yeah, what are you gonna do? You're a pedophile, but you were just calling me a pimp remember?
You know what? You are
Why would Gato's name be Brandon Q?
Brandon Q?
What did you say?
What did you say about Chris King?
Even though Gato was a white Chris King, what did you say?
You told Chris King that he fucked the black babies.
She kills the black babies, buddy.
He does.
She does.
And what do you got us like, boy?
Well, you got a little mask on.
She does.
And what are you going to do about it, bro?
What are you going to do about it, bro?
What are you going to do about it?
What are you going to do about it, Doug?
That's what I'm gonna do. That's exactly what J-Dawg gonna do.
I'm gonna sit here and laugh at your ass, you fucking queer.
What are you gonna do about it?
Why are you so upset?
What are you gonna do?
I mean, you don't get to push me.
I do.
I get to push you on video.
I get to push you on video, by the way.
I'll catch yourself to my dick while I'm on video, bro.
Okay, I agree with you.
Mad bitches.
Yeah, I can't.
I can show you videos.
I'm gonna go with that right now.
Yeah.
Do you have 500? I know your broke ass does not have 500 bucks.
You don't even know money. You just a fucking, you just a little fucking creep and a fucking...
You a little creepy.
You a little clown. Nigger, you a little bit of a monkey-ass.
Look at your dick.
Nigger, look at you. I get bitches. You don't.
You don't get pussy.
Have you ever heard your voice, dude? That's a bigotore from bitches, bro. You get no pussy.
Where'd he go?
Come on
He left what a bitch man, it was getting good
Why do you have that mask on like what do you think he was gonna go to try to pull up on do that guy is not hard
He's not a game sure he ain't about that. Hey, let me just tell you that anybody can go and buy a bunch of
Um in minecraft and minecraft cut psyche because I don't want your channel here or none
Pellet guns and go buy all this this stuff that looks like they're real real
You know water pistols back. He's back. He's back. Oh, he's back. Okay. Let him back up psyche
Yeah, you think just because you have a couple of a are you think you're
Dog and then come come over here
Yeah, yeah, you are you are you are
Oh, no, you're in my neck.
You're calling me a pain.
Look at you.
You're in my neck.
Prove it. Why don't you come over to Cali?
Show your bank account, show your bank account.
Why don't you come to Cali?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, yes.
Oh, they're so tough.
You're going to have veins.
Come pull up to me, veins.
Pull up to a real man.
And you know, there's a lot in the stream.
You know, there's a psyche as a minor mod.
You are the minor mod. That's who you are. You are the minor. I shouldn't be up here talking to you Brendan
You are scum Brendan
Come pull up the J-dog and then we'll see what I'm gonna do about it
When are you going to pull up?
When are you going to pull up, Doug?
You know my location.
Help me. When are you going to pull up?
Pull up with your little fat gay son.
Come with me. Pull up with your little fat gay son.
Where are you at, bro?
200 General Marshall.
Help me pull up.
Two hundred two hundred general Marshall faggot. No somebody out right now. Hey, you come up with your fat-ass son, bro
Two hundred general
200 General Marshall, 200 General Marshall, do something.
Bring your fat-ass ugly son.
Wait, hey, can you tell me more or less of where you're at, Brandon Q?
If you want J-Doc to pull up, I'll be more than happy to pull up.
200 General Marshall, 200 General Marshall.
Give me the cross-screeks. What are the cross-screeks about?
200 General Marshall, Albuquerque, New Mexico.
Is that your address or is that a place where you're at right now?
I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to know where you're at right now, I want to
You will push the ass nigga, I want to show you all the time, you are a fake tough guy.
I want you to do something, when are you gonna do something?
A couple of AR's you think you're a badass nigga, I will kick your ass on you and I will
fucking hit you with the fucking butt of it.
That's how much of a badass J-Gawd is.
That's how much of a badass J-Gawd is, I won't even need to fire that big.
I'll take it right from your hands and hit you in the fucking face with the butt of it.
Then do it.
And not get a fucking on you, but be about it.
Where you at?
Show location nigger right outside
I'm driving there if you ain't really there
I'll kiss you, that's right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the side right, I'm on the
but i have homies that will i got homies that are around there a lot of homies
i got a lot of homies so i need to know what you really want i need to know what you're wearing
that was a motherfuckers pull up on you they fucking got your ass they got your general
You are fucking lit to get your ass beat the fuck up, and your gun's taken from you.
You understand me?
That's something.
I do it.
That's what's going to happen, you know what I'm going to do is take it right from your hand and then you know what I'm going to do, I'm going to run your pockets too.
I'm going to run your pockets too. It's like you say you got money, I'm going to run your pockets. Okay.
When though? But when? The minute you turn the camera on and show me what the fuck you're at. Okay, turn the camera on and let's see what you're at.
I can lie and make up an address too nigga, I can lie and make up an address too, I'm really, I'm not, but let me see if you're really there, let me see if you're really there, show me if you're really there, you were scaring me, you were scaring me, you were scaring me, why are you so scared, go see.
Nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice excuse, nice
She said Alex would send you a grand if I put PENGOT on it.
Now you're going to say four grand by the way, four grand.
Can you show proof of that?
Just like you can show proof of your location, right?
Show proof of your location.
show me proof of your house show the front of your house
door-dash bro show the front of your house exactly reality nancy no yep yep
Hey, she didn't give you anything. No, no, no, that's a lie. You know, maybe maybe she did go
five bucks, a dollar, maybe even it has to be under 20 bucks because you ain't worth more than
20 bucks. Dude, you're a pedophile, bro. No, you are. You're a pedophile, bro. You're a pedophile.
You sound like you ran out of shit. You ain't that bright, huh? You ain't that bright
We look at you also says Alex wanted him as a baby dad
Dude, you are like two chromosomes away from being fucking
Did we mentally make you that you wanted my DNA nigga? You are retarded you slow, dude
Why would any bitch want to have a replicate with you nigga? You slow like to make more slow retarded pedophile babies fuck that
Hell no, nobody would get that.
The fact that you was in your car,
making your deliveries, right?
Amazon delivery, bitch.
Yeah.
You are
That's what you ain't gonna do shit.
You ain't gonna do nada, bro.
I'mma sit right here.
I'mma sit right here, smoking this good Cali weed.
And watch your way.
You ain't gonna knock the fuck out of me.
You don't got it.
You ain't gonna do shit, bro.
You ain't gonna take it.
You're under general.
Don't go under general Marshall.
You ain't gonna do nothing.
You're under general Marshall.
You ain't general Marshall.
You ain't there, though.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
The only one scared scared I just dropped it 200 general Marshall bro. You like that right now though. Drop that you know where you're at
I know you're not you're making 100 general Marshall right now 200 general Marshall
wearing a little faggot mask like it's covid 2020 again
You and you fucking cuz you don't want nobody to see you cuz you're fucking gonna get your ass whooped
Because everybody knows you you're fucking freak and creep over there. So yeah, I'd be
Nobody likes you. Hey, hey, j-dog. How can everybody punks you and clowns on me, bro?
You're a joke, dawg.
Everybody punks and clowns on you, bro, with your class towelette.
Your class towelette.
You got a class towelette, homie.
You got a class towelette, dawg.
Have you looked in the mirror brain and you can't even grow a beard, dude
You got no you got no is kestrel any of your blood or DNA you ain't man
You're a little boy and jade all don't fuck with little boys like you
And too much of a fucking badass to fuck with someone that is a fucking pedophile like you Brandon
You are a pedophile you're in a pedophile stream where there's a minor mod
Where are you? Where are you?
You're on the same fucking screen, supposedly.
I'm here to fucking laugh at you.
Supposedly. Supposedly.
I got rid of this.
No, you're a fucking fruitcake driving around
delivering an Amazon package.
I'm walking down the hood.
I'm trying to argue.
Trying to argue, but you're just going to get your ass beat the minute I get to location. What'd you hit?
200 general Marshall walking
Did you 100 general Marshall with me?
200 general Marshall dog. We're gonna pull up make a sweating. I guarantee I got him sweating. Oh, yeah
Keep talking dog. Keep talking
Keep talking pedophile. Let me get where you're at though. Don't get me to enter general marshal either bitch
Remember get up your phone number backstage. Yeah, remember what was my number?
Hey, I'm gonna find out where you work, and I'm gonna take
Don't big the other day pussy
When you're back when you're back in psyche
Docs my phone number if you have my phone I guarantee you remember you're begging psyche to fuck you at a gay club remember
Remember, you were begging him to meet up with you at a gay club and fuck you, and you gave him your number.
I'm arguing with a little kid here, psyche. I'm arguing with a little kid here, man.
Hey, remember you wanted to go to a gay nightclub with a gay cat, bro.
You were in the fifth grade of a fifth grade, and you weren't getting animals on.
nigger you work at amazon you fuck you remember you wanted to go to a gate
nightclub with a gate bedroom focus your little fork focus and thank you about
what you hit a telephone pole again we're walking into shit
we're walking
So why do you rape kids J-Dog? Why do you rape your own niece? That's what I heard
Somebody's some of these message you mean right now J-Dog saying that you rape your own niece dog
Is that true by the way? I don't even have a new so that's even more
Prove it
Why is everybody saying that you raped your own niece?
Oh, that's the word going around now,
that you raped your own niece.
Sure, Brandon, sure.
And whatever you say, really, whatever you say.
You're like clumsy, bro.
You're a netbanger.
You're like clumsy, a netbanger.
You're a jimmy mod.
You're a punk, bro.
OK, yeah.
You're a coward, bro.
What happened?
You're a sure jimmy mod.
You don't know shit about me Brandon. Okay, you don't know everything about you bro. I know how you raped your niece
Well, I live at then what do I do?
Okay, yeah, cool. Okay. Yeah, I live in LA County come get who come get me
No, I'm not a scrap home. Yeah, you are. No, I'm not get my wearing blue, bitch. No, that's how stupid you are stupid fuck
They dog never rocks blue so get that to your head. That's how much you know about
Why'd you rape your own niece? You're a sewer rat, bro
Can you come up with some or at come up with some more insults at least come back. I'll go back to the cliff
Why do you live in sewer Kelly? Why do you live in sewer Kelly?
Why do you live in? Why do you live in a D? Why do you live in Clovis, New Mexico?
You're a sewer rat, bro. You're a sewer rat. Why do you live in sewer side? Oh, why do you live on the sewer side?
Mm-hmm. Suicide. Why do you live on the suicide, bro?
You couldn't afford Cali.
You were fucking...
You couldn't afford Cali, bro.
You live on the suicide, bro.
You were a suicider, bro.
Cali's only for the cool people, like me and Psyche.
And Vita, the people who live in Cali, that's where it's at.
The West Coast is where it's at.
You ain't West Coast.
So the suicide.
You desert puns, bro.
You fucking live in the desert.
So you're a suicider.
See, no water, nothing, homie.
You are creepy, dude. You're very creepy one last time, Brandon
Bro, that's what I want to know though. They don't gonna do any of that. I don't even have a knee
You rape your own niece, bro
Can you please turn on your camera? I want to see that goofy ass fucking
You fucking pussy
No, I don't want to go back I don't want to go to your house
Where you have rights
Meet me in a street, in a fucking public park street.
God, I don't wanna beat you on no house.
Meet me in a store, meet me somewhere,
not your house.
When you have rights, pussy,
well, you're gonna try to fucking shoot me.
And then try to say, oh, self-defense.
Don't pull out a bullet.
J-Dog, don't fall for root card bullshit right there.
I'll make sure, bro.
Fall for root card bullshit,
and that's only something root cards pull.
Why is that the excuse that I want everybody to pull up to my house where I have a pistol and I could shoot you stupid?
I'll shoot you anywhere, bro. I don't need to be in my house to shoot you.
You don't need to carry anything. Why do I need to be in my house to shoot you?
You don't carry. You don't carry.
Prove it.
Okay, okay. Prove it.
Click something right now. Click something right now. Click that racket right now.
Prove it. Prove it.
What do you want?
Prove it.
Not your seat belt. Don't rack your seat belt. Don't rack your seat belt. You're just clapping your seat belt
Don't do that. Yeah, you want to hear a clap? You want to hear a clap?
Do you want to hear a stop dog?
Show what's that?
What's that?
Show it.
What's that, dog?
Show it, dog.
You think you're tough.
Show it.
Let me see that.
What's that?
That's your seatbelt nigga
Stop doing that. You're like a little kid play with your seatbelt you stop it
What's that?
Have you really got it kill it
Fucking hot though, bro. You're a hot though. You're a hot though
Baggett Filipino, bro. You know, you know, you feel a Pino
You know, you don't even have full Latin blood in you. You are Filipino
You were Filipino. I see your muckshot. You look like
You look all scared like a
Hey, what do you think taking in for me? What do you really get go for it? Have you think you really?
Would you go down for?
You go down for raping your mom
That's what I went down for what are you gonna do about quit messing with your seatbelt branding you pussy-ass nigger stop all that
Yeah, bitch imagine being born with a cleft palate. What God hates you. Oh, I'm a good
That's even worse to be born with you
You know and Brandon Q's body, that's the worst fucking thing ever that's more hell than waking up with me
Can you imagine what it's like to not bring friends with you?
I'm not fucking...
You fucking...
What are you fucking doing?
I'm not fucking...
You're a pussy.
Done.
You're the epitome of Ink Cell.
That's Ink Cell.
That's who you are.
Ink Cell.
Ink Cell, homie.
You're an Ink Cell.
Bitch, nigga.
You don't get
The horse man on your screen look at him you see him
Yeah, well, he's getting fucked by a horse or he's fucking a horse I'm guessing it's the other way around
Yeah, did you see him bro? What a pussy-ass nigga, huh?
Dude, he won't even give me his location or cam up dude. He's over there delivering Amazon dude
He just docks his own job. He's over there delivering Amazon packages wearing those little masks like elbow wares
Delivering packages that's why he's scared to give me a location. That's why he can't even give me a solid location
I mean he can but he's too scared to do it. Yeah
Yeah, like what a fucking but like dude that guy all he thinks about is kids like what the fuck I don't I mean
I think it's just from like
The like the bullying and stuff, but I don't I know he's turned on me
What was it that they were trying to say that Brandon was like botting or like pain like bought your views or some shit or like your
What the heck would they would they just be views or there would actually be people like typing in the chat
Oh, he came back now
Is he is he gonna stop is he gonna stop with the way getting fucking the horse
Okay, did he bust a good one in you or what Brandon?
Did you get a good one in you or what?
That horse good to give a good load of stuff?
I'm getting all your information.
There's all of it, bro.
Your mom's going to end up getting fucked after this.
You're a little kid, homie.
You're a little kid.
But would you really drive the J-Dog and meet J-Dog?
I highly doubt you would.
Hey, psyche, how's the AIDS treating you?
You're a fucking piece of shit, psyche. You're a scumbag, bro.
You know that?
Are you taking me off? Like, oh, hold on.
Bye, because Joker comes on that motherfucker.
Don't even give a fuck about you, bro.
Where's he at now?
I made you, bro. I made you and watch.
Now your channel is going to fucking die, bro.
Hey, you didn't make nobody.
You can't even make your beard.
You can't even make yourself.
Make yourself bro. Why are you over here? Why don't you stream it on your own panel?
If why are you over here trying to tell psyche as age trying to talk shit to me when you a known pedophile me?
Prove it I've seen videos prove it. I don't bring up gamble either. Do not bring that guy
Yeah
And like you just been nigga you've been eggs to the community ever since you came you don't understand
This community whoever brought you here, they should take their ass back
But we don't want you here. We don't want you. I need you here, bro
Go back to you little pedophile gamers shit and stay over there. We don't we don't fuck with you
So you can answer me. Why'd you rape your niece?
The panel burst does not fuck with Brandon Q.
So why did you rape your niece, J-Darg?
So you dropped me a location?
I don't have this allegation. I don't like to get fired.
I mean, he keeps talking about kids.
Yeah, he keeps talking about kids, man. He's gross.
Okay, hold on. Clumsy's back and maybe we'll move on.
Do you want to talk to him?
So Luke's the closest.
Yeah, where's he at?
Oh, he ran, bro. Oh, wait, is he back?
There he is. I'm on my meeting.
Hey little sushi, are you mad cause you don't got no friends?
Oh, oh Brandon, you can't wait to go and talk to your boss, huh?
Hey clumsy, hey clumsy. Hey, why don't you come with your fat ass son, bro?
Why don't you come with your fat fuck son?
I love you, I am next. I love you. Please don't talk to me like that, I am next.
Yeah, exactly now look at this. Look at this fucking coward. He's a bitch. Why do you run? Why do you run?
Nobody ran.
I'm just curious why he runs.
What's the deal with you?
Why'd you come back and crawl under the fucking rock you came out of?
What do you run?
Why do you run nigga? Why don't you just go back and your little fucking hole and go fuck with your gaming shit?
And just leave everybody and the powers alone. Why don't you just make me dog? Why don't you make me, bro?
Why don't you make me?
Well drop location and we'll see about that and don't get
Don't give me your house drop the location of where you're at right now like legit right now
You know all you got to do is just stay location on your thing and then just pinpoint it on Google and I can see
Don't even come and look at you. Just give me your coordinates. I just need your coordinates
Tell me where you're at 200 general Marshall. No
wrong answer
All right, man. Shut the fuck up wrong answer
You're too scared to show where you're really at you won't even do he won't even came up
Frankie, how did you deal with that guy, bro?
My god, dude, that guy's a nutcase like what the fuck dude
I hope he is too scared to drop his location cuz he knows so many people would just pull up on him and just fuck him up like
Why did he have to come up with it?
Who brought him around dude?
Like honestly Psyche, where did you see this guy come from?
All of a sudden?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Know
Yeah, he's crossing the line bro. He crosses the line big time like he's gonna bring up kids and shit
Yeah, I can't hear you psychic coming in and out man
Yeah, you wanna let him up
Can you just go back to the hole you crawled out of like please hey come see who's this little ugly fat fucker look at this little ugly
Dude, he's doxing pictures of kids
Dude, I yeah
The only cute thing about his own photo as a kid, nobody else can, not Brandon here, but the other two of us.
Yeah, yeah, I know who it is.
Yeah.
He went to like a beach, and he's like more than the same.
Alex, he's like, oh my god, you're so romantic.
Okay guys, I'll do a poll in the chat.
Do you even if you ban him he's gonna come back on a different account. Yeah, he does that bro
He makes multiple account. He's a fucking dude. He's like an incel troll who don't have no friends. He
Wants to be liked by everybody. He's trying to fit in but for one. He's a creep
He I just creep vibes all the way, bro
Like he has that fucking effeminate voice like he looks like he hasn't hit puberty yet
um
I mean, his breasts are fully grown.
Okay, well, yeah, true.
Look Howard, bro. Yeah, ban me bro ban me that ain't gonna stop nothing bro. You saw Tony was bad. Hey, bro
We guess what I know how to do shit without getting caught boy. I know
We'll get the court all this shit right here and we'll just give it to
You just threaten psyche so yeah
Okay, cool, so you said another
Versus another stalker. Okay, cool. You want to do that? Okay, cool. Go for it
So I could do that do that brandy to see how that works out for you want to know something Jay
Doug, maybe you might want to go figure out why all the troll communities all this and that why they don't they don't even
They don't even attempt to fuck with me, bro. Go figure that out
Go figure that out. What do you mean worth it?
You're not even worth that
Nobody even wants to go near you!
You know what it is? It's like you're the homeless person on the screen with things like shit
and you're taking a shit on the screen.
We're gonna walk completely around you
and you're gonna be like, yeah, yeah, people are afraid of me, they don't want to fuck with me.
Yeah, look at you! Who was it?
Who was it?
Yeah, what are you gonna do about it, bro?
Who was it, nigga?
Who was it?
Hey, Colby!
Hey, Colby, pull up with your little fat fuck son so he can get it too, bro.
Well, drop it in your little fat book.
Drop the location. Where you're rolling at right now.
Where you really at right now?
Go give your fucking house that grass pussy.
Where you really at right now? Give cross-screets.
I'm at my house.
No, I'm at my house, sir.
Okay, okay. Can you bring your camera on and show us where you're at your house?
What do you need? What do you need it?
Why don't you go home sometime?
Hey, hey, hey!
What I gotta go I gotta go home sometime, right? I'll be live sitting on my computer at home and what are you gonna do about it, bro?
What are you gonna do? So should we have people beat you up before you enter your house or after your head on your house?
You hide
Oh
Fuck god, bitch you a pussy ass nigger Brandon you scared and why are you so scared?
Why you afraid you afraid to fight somebody you afraid to get your ass beat because that's what you really need is a good ass
That's exactly what you need. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. You're sitting at your house. How are you gonna be my ass when you're sitting at your house?
You gave me your location now people there in five seconds
Where are you at right now, where are you at right now where are you at right now
You're too scared you won't even come up and show me your your house you pussy trying to give me your house address
But don't even give me it was a fucking idiot. You were walking around with you thought that that was your backup
Bro that guy's a legit Looney Tunes, bro. He's loco in the cocoa bro. He's fucking crazy
Yeah, bro, he's nuts man good dude those are the people this guy is try to stay away from bro because those people are fucking
mm-hmm
They got more than one one screw loose if you know what I mean
And he takes it as a badge of honor why nobody fucks with them like
Dude, who would even want to talk to him like look at him look what he talks about
I can't hear you psyche you're I think you're far away from your life
Yeah, I hear you know
Respective than you. There's always got I don't know. Yeah, it's like let's be the kid talk
Alright, you're gonna go you're gonna drop location. Hello Richard you there. What's up coward Richard? Hey, what's up coward?
Are you ready to give me where you're at your cross streets, so we can meet up and fight
Are you ready to give me your cross streets so we can
Scrap
Yeah, and tell clumsy to come with this little fat fuck ugly ass fucking son bro, so you could get it to
Yo, I'll be back. Oh, yeah, that's what I thought
craziness
It's the same backstage
Hold on, J-Dog, don't let Psyche lie to you.
He invited Brandon here with open arms.
People warned him, I warned him.
He didn't listen and it cost him his channel.
That's why this channel is dead.
Well, the channel's not dead.
There's like 42 people in here right now.
I know he's not bodying the thing,
so, and also it cost him my channel,
where I have my channel, RG.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Actually, I have three channels.
and they're alive.
It's alive, it's alive, I know.
But you know who this channel did die at you?
Or YouTube channel died at RG?
I'm so sorry, you're on Rumble, right?
Aw.
Okay.
I know, now I see who he is.
Yeah, you're only here to watch J-Dog versus Brandon.
Well, you're not here to watch me?
Get out of here.
Well, get out of here.
I don't want you in here doping out.
You're timed out.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm the star of the show.
You can go see them, you know.
I'm on Grand Marshal and whatever Street Fruit Street or whatever. I don't know
Okay, well
Because everyone hates me though 49 people. Okay. Whoo. That's pretty cool. Well, welcome to the show guys. Thank you for coming
You know, I'm still here. I'm still okay. So let me see
I just want to show you, you know, see if you're in the guys I did this I did this one
And it's like, you know, there's a lot of people like or in the show and it see if you can recognize the people because oh my god
There's I've got the antlers right here. Oh my god. Okay. Um,
Let me see. I don't know. Um, so how are we doing? I don't know. Maybe I'm
Getting a little
Weary of all this like, you know silliness, but oh
Gosh, oh gosh. Oh gosh. Okay
Yeah, so this is this is what I'm talking about here. I'll bear it back shortly back after these commercial
to the transmission. Yeah. That means you know. Oh, well. Oh, well. I'm going to quit
Danny. I won't tell. I won't tell.
Beaters got the biscuits and ready for your sale tonight. Beast kid gang come running got
the band. Freeman beater come back one more time. Thunder at the window Nancy rodin on
the rain. Pull the magician manifest and defend and psych his name. She got time to
I don't even know his panel box. Just froze again connection. Oh, and there we go
Officer Alex McQueen your man
Smoke machine and cuffs are trolling drags. I'm off the wrong redeemer. They threw the arrows through the hate
I caught him in the light night. Oh, do I wanted him to be not who he is
That's the night. Let's Kate again Tony's on the tribe. You know, but he's gonna jamey sulking
I think he's banned.
I think that was his banality.
I think it's like, I think it's enough.
I think enough is enough.
And that's for like, you know,
oh my gosh, everyone is leaving, everyone's leaving.
First of all, it's none of their business.
Hi, Nolan, how are you?
It's none of their business.
It's like, it's my business, okay?
So the second of all, it's just annoying.
It's like, people can see the numbers and stuff like that.
So it's like, shut up or I'll make you shut up.
I'm banning you from the fucking chat.
Geez.
It's like the same people too.
I mean, it's like, oh my God.
It's like he has AIDS, it's like he's spinging your nails.
You're a trans guy?
Wow.
I think I was showing Buck Angel the other day.
You know, Buck Angel is a trans man.
Here's what he looks like.
He was born a woman and he does porn,
where his vagina is.
It's very confusing. Hi Chanel, hi Chanel, hi sweetie, but it's like the tattoos are a little bit feminine like right?
I think I think maybe like this. I don't know but wow those muscles, right? You're born for me just like a guy
I just like a guy sometimes. Yeah, I know you don't physically threaten. So you're fine. You're fine
Okay, how are we doing? What else do I have and guys that wasn't like, you know that picture of like that Mexican guy with the red ball in his mouth
I found the original video that's from this not like a gay website. It's it's a
He does like balloon
animals and stuff like that
for parties and
You can actually
You know
See the original video. It's not a red ball in the mouth. It's a balloon
It's really cool how he blows up to he is able to like in midair let the balloon out of his mouth and then cash it again
Good to see you to Nolan
Good to see you too.
We'll met and see, no, now I've gotten into it.
Now people think that you're, see, I don't know.
I don't know.
I know you're, I know you're, what's your picture?
What's in that in your picture?
Hold on, it's okay.
Oh, what is that?
I can barely see it, hold on.
Oh, is that you flexing?
I see an arm.
See that's an adult arm.
I don't know.
Okay.
It's muscle, okay.
I got some muscle too, I got some muscle.
Yep, yep, yep.
Okay, so perfect.
yeah so anyway and also you know sometimes when people have guests like you know people
like to see the guests and it's like you know people are gonna be interested in different things
certainly i have not been alone the entire time even if there's just been people like you know
mad dogging me and trying to give me evil eye i still got views and algorithm actually i'm still
in the top 10% of youtube creators on the channel that i'm not even posting videos on right now
on my main channel and so it's like what the fuck i mean it's like i'm doing fine
I'm doing fine. Okay. So what do I have? Let me see. Oh my gosh. Okay. Yeah, so I'm gonna
Oh, yeah, I want to show you don't see like who I'll do. I'll do this like Illuminati like a tutorial for you
Okay, so there's a guy named Othlian Childs and he was on I guess New Zealand or Australia he was on a show called the voice
But then he came out and said, oh my god, you have to hear about all the Freemasons Freemasons.
And it's like, and then he has a whole story and a song and dance about it.
But I think he's a Freemason. But we'll see. Here you go.
These same symbols appear in our pockets.
The disembodied eye watching from the top of the pyramid on a dollar bill
points toward an interconnected system of symbols that spans centuries.
For those tracking these patterns, the trail leads back to one organization,
the Secret Fraternal Order of Freemasonry.
Publicly, the masons appear as a network of local lodges,
aging men in aprons who fund children's hospitals and run local charities.
This diagram outlines the structure of the order.
The charitable exterior serves as the wide bottom layer of a hierarchy designed to satisfy the public.
To find control, believers look past the local lodge,
climbing the pyramid into the restricted degrees of the initiated.
The middle tiers of the pyramid function as a multi-level screening process.
This is a filter used to vet politicians, corporate leaders, and Hollywood stars before they reach the top.
Control is maintained through a series of blood oaths.
Initiates swear to have their throats cut or their tongues torn out
if they ever reveal the secrets shared within the Lodge.
The physical space of the Lodge reinforces a dualistic worldview.
This checkered floor symbolizes a space where traditional morals are balanced
and eventually reversed.
High-ranking members reaching the 33rd degree, seen here on the sash of Albert Pike,
reach a level where the theory claims traditional iconography is abandoned.
This filtering system ensures that the people managing global institutions
have already agreed to compromise their previous moral framework.
At these levels, the order allegedly reveals the royal art,
a hidden religion based in witchcraft and Luciferian philosophies.
Esoteric philosophies from figures like Alistair Crowley are integrated here.
The eye in triangle symbol on Crowley's hat visually mirrors the imagery used across the
Order's hierarchy. High-ranking initiates are allegedly required by their oaths to display
their presence in the public sphere through specific signals. For modern musicians and
celebrities, this manifests as the all-seeing eye covering one eye and hand gestures that signify
Historical leaders and heads of state used a different signal, the hidden hand,
where one hand is tucked into a jacket or shirt to acknowledge their membership.
In this worldview, these markers are functional signals.
They serve as public acknowledgments of a hidden power structure operating in plain sight.
At the very top of the hierarchy is the capstone.
This represents the fulfillment of the great work,
the long-term objective mentioned in esoteric literature.
One primary objective involves completely replacing our traditional morality with a new system,
one based entirely on a survival of the fittest law of nature.
The second objective addresses a world moving toward automated labor.
As people become redundant to the economic system,
the plan allegedly calls for a massive reduction in the global population.
Physical evidence of this goal was carved into the Georgia Guidestones.
The first instruction on the monument demands that humanity be maintained at a population
under 500 million. This great work describes a transition toward a centralized one-world government,
the New World Order. This sprawling mega-conspiracy remains resilient because it attempts to answer
the most difficult questions of our time. It takes the real-world anxieties of extreme wealth
and of automation, and projects them onto a single identifiable group.
It thrives because it replaces random chaos with a sense of design.
It suggests that the world's problems aren't accidents,
but parts of a dark, unstoppable plan that only the believer has the vision to see.
Okay, so that was, I mean, I can show you another little diagram,
Here's a diagram kind of explaining a little bit more, okay
So we have a so it's called the great work
Salve coagula
This is I mean, there's other secret societies too, but they're kind of under the same umbrella
Right. Okay. So we have the all-seeing eye hidden hands libraries and politicians displaying it the 666 hand gesture
See how it makes three sixes. Okay. We have the square and compass versus a sexual act the g stands for generative principle, right?
Which is reproduction basically and so we have the iceberg structure, you know, they say we this is only a tip of the iceberg
So so source claims 75 to 90% of members are intentionally misled by false
Interpretations of symbols while the
while the remaining, true remaining is reserved
for the princes of Freemasonry on the 33rd degree.
They also have a filtering process.
And so it looks like, you know,
they're donating money to hospitals,
like the Shriners and stuff,
nice little clowns driving around in cars.
But they call actually in the bottom rung,
the part where the pyramid you can't actually see,
or I guess we're underwater, you know,
it's kind of like, you ever see the little mermaid?
So most people are under the water,
like they're mermaids and stuff like that.
and it's like they want legs but then they have to go make a deal with fucking Ursula who's an octopus
and so that's like and then you lose your voice right I mean so it's a whole thing right but look
it so there's a secret religion in the middle
with Lucifer as a light bearer and then you know the royal art is witchcraft called the royal
art because I guess blood rituals and calling spiritual entities I guess has been the royal
practice. So what do we have? Order out of chaos. We also have a PRS which is problem reaction
solution or the Hegelian dialect. We have solved Calagula. Oh my god. Plan to dissolve the current
coagulated into a new, higher form of esoteric system.
The final climax, ultimate goal.
Worldwide system and singular government
where the vulgar of Lucifer,
or sorry, the car of Lucifer rules over the vulgar multitude.
The car is like the...
The ambassador of the prince and there's a silence and so they'll say you know you'll have your tongue cut out
And you know all the stuff if you take these oaths and so people are afraid but basically
They make it economically advantage and your advantage to like you know keep your oaths and stuff like that
You don't want me kicked out
lead after a planned salvation
It increases their control solution. Yeah, so the PRS is a leak create a
Explicit catastrophic problem. Oh, he made me. There's my abuser gone. Oh, no, it's okay. I don't care
I'm not gonna a controversial topic more than half left. I don't care what but you get your robots in here
You're the loser brand and you're a loser and you're banned from the show. So go away. You don't want to talk backstage
Don't be such a little bitch
It's not a dead stream. Dead streams have zero people dead show
Well, if it's if it's dead then you help to kill but you know what?
I have the power of Jesus to resurrect and Lazarus is returning and you know who's dead your appearances
Yeah, God moment. I leave everyone left. Nobody cares about my oh, they don't okay. They don't okay
Well, I got so much good feedback about you being a brand it's a much good feedback
So, you know, I'm sure it was I'm sure was you that brought all the interest to the show you literally nobody gives a damn
Hold on. Oh, you can't because you can't say that on my regular chat
So you have to say enjoy irrelevant aides boy. Okay, Brandon. Go enjoy your one viewer
Go enjoy your Q army, which is just bots. I mean you are just so pathetic Brandon and it's like wow
Why did I even give you a chance? I don't know. I must have been
Fucking retarded temporarily, but you know what I learned fast not not fast, but I eventually do learn
Okay, so go scream in the back little bitch
Anyway, jeez, I'm okay, so we're gonna gong off-brain permanently from the show.
This is no requiring no donation or anything, I'm just gonna gong brain off.
Man, bitch, out of here.
Going on a little show, Kermit the Frog or Pee Wee, whatever your name is, I don't know.
He's like across between Pee Wee, Kermit the Frog, and John Wayne Gacy, he's awful.
What's my problem?
Oh my god, okay.
So now my show is a gong show, I got a couple more people, 17 people, oh no, they all left Brandon, I'm sorry, all your bots, you know, they all left because you probably said.
I don't want bots anyway. There's 12 people here. I want to see 12 people
I don't see 50 people and you then you then you lie to yourself and say they're real people that are here for you
And they're just your Q army. We know what the Q army is
It's like some robots you bought from Dayton, Ohio on a monthly subscription bitch. We know you God
Anyway, oh so much fun
But he didn't he didn't reveal that I am actually a woman. I was born a woman
He knows all I mean he figured out my AIDS thing. I don't know how I figure out how I had AIDS
I mean, I haven't I never
Publicized anything like it like saying that but you know, he says it must be true. I know he has a greater reputation
Anyhow, so how are we doing today? What is today Monday? We're having a great Monday
Monday is the day of the moon
It's the actually like mono means one
But it's actually the second day of the week if you take Sunday is the first day and God created everything on Sunday
So maybe God's the Sun or something. I don't know. I don't know what they're trying to say to us through that, but um
Let me see. What do I got? You have AI flop even if I've shown like
Actual like I've showed other video. I play a lot of content on my show
I think and everyone think everyone's like is this AI it's like most of it's not even AI then it's not even mine
It's like but it's like oh they'll just because they think it's I you know
It's something that has to do with me then they're gonna say it's terrible and stuff because you're just a bunch of trolls
They're so stupid
And my troll. Oh my god. I'm the king of the trolls just by blood. I mean, but I'm actually I've overcome my trolldom
You know, I've no need let's say that's I need to use it. It's good. It's a good defense skill once in a while
But not a way to live your life. I mean geez
Sad you get okay
So, okay
Let's see what I got for us
I got some good ones. Whoo. It's warm today. It is so warm
Mmm. It's uh, yeah, it's a beautiful day though. Oh
Hmm. Yeah, so Alex McQueen won't be back ghost came back, but I don't think I don't think ghosts likes me anymore
I mean, it's like it's okay. It's okay. I don't need to be I don't need to be loved by anybody
I do love myself
So I'll be okay. I I do have my cult of my cult always been a cult of one
Well, I had two people one point, but I think the the Oracle left me in a lurch, but it's okay
There's always another Oracle
I'm hiring oracles, so you can submit your application.
If you'd like to join the team, okay.
Yeah, check out Cool Codex, by the way, guys,
is looking pretty freaking good.
Okay.
I think this is the one I was trying to show you here.
You think I suck so bad?
Well, check this out.
Hi, oh, hi, INX, how are you?
You want the link?
Okay, got you.
Just give me a second to,
Just show something real quick, and I'll have you right up. Hi. I love you, sweetie. There you go
Closer, say the name, so truthfully I was born always standing where it's gonna burn through
My hunger isn't gold, it's a sound of a system of, as for the ones that we've been waiting for
Where the air still breathes, it's gonna live on through me
As folk, it interrupts the environment, one clean strife, throws a sleep and lies, and is she a-
Hey, hey Inax! I'm sorry, thank you for letting me play it.
Let me take it off. Hello, INX, are you there? Paging INX. I can't hear you. Hello? INX.
Enjoy your relevance. Oh my god. INX, I have to show you what Brandon is going crazy. He says,
nobody gives a damn about me. Everyone's just here for him. He made me... I had a...
Before he came around I had an okay show. I mean, it's like he's I mean, what he's gonna he's gonna ruin my show
Then he's gonna yell at me. I mean, I mean, maybe this is my fault for having him on because this is dumbass. I mean jeez
You'll come back. Okay, sweetie. Thank you. Okay. I'm sorry. Thank you for I'm sorry
I didn't mean to be so long but you know
Now is a sponsored message. I just wanted to show you that I'm actually like, you know, there's something more to me than just like
You know
Nothing. He's nuts. He's nuts
Mean I can say I can handle crazy people but not just like dumb and crazy people when they're dumb and crazy
Then it's like I can't take smart crazy people are okay
Yes, yeah. Oh my god. Enjoy relevance AIDS boy first of all
I mean, no, who gets AIDS at him. No, no one gets AIDS in the in the country
I mean, it's like isn't it been eradicated for like 20 years or so. I mean, I don't know
I know people can still get it, but it's like
Just have you does anybody get it anymore? I don't even think people get it. They get HIV over the sig medication and it's like
You know, it takes the takes even the HIV out of your system. So I don't understand what they're talking about
But anyway, who cares who cares we all we all know about MAO and hipidermis and stuff like that
But I'm not here to explain everything. So yeah, he's nuts. He's nuttier than you know, fucking Chippendale
geez
You take prep preparation H booty goon
Or you're saying you have a tube. I'm sorry if you have a STD. See, I haven't had enough sex to even have an STD
I think you have to look I think it is. I mean, I'm I'm really like not really done anything that risky
unless that woman I slept with you know, I
Dried too much for menstrual fluid and she might have had a disease, but I don't think she did. I really don't think she did
But anyway, but I do think that spaghetti recipe with the extra iron is a winner. Oh my god
But anyway, this is who Brandon can date.
Go ahead and date Buck Angel, please.
Leave me alone.
There we go.
But I do thank him for like, you know,
it's an HIV medication.
Well, I'm sorry, doesn't it?
But you have to take it every day.
Are you serious or not?
I mean, it's like, I do know, oh my God.
Oh, yeah, okay, good.
Okay, I and X is here.
Hi.
Can you hear me now?
Yeah.
Okay, good. I don't know what was wrong. I guess my Bluetooth. I had to turn it off because I was out
Yeah, you know what I feel bad for Alex
But it seemed that she turned on me and she knew that I had a good convo with her dad when somebody had his
Gave his information and stuff and he asked me to call him. I have the text
I thought I showed it to her where he said can you please call me because the text ended up nice where I told him I was in
uh, where he was and uh, you know, he was upset at somebody's wife calling him
So he wanted to talk on the phone and I have the text. He says can you please call me? Yeah, and I did
She is on her show. She she she told the whole story about how thankful she was towards you how it's great
Yeah, and that's and we had a good convo and he was a nice nice man that loved his daughter said she was his favorite
They were close. She was like him wonderful daughter and stuff
And then he was the cool and so he was care. He cared about that streamer son
That was sick and he cared enough to say hey
Tell him about the MDN, they're sending hospitals, the best place for cancer here in the states.
And I said, well, they're not here in Texas, they're in another state.
You know, he said, oh, okay, you know, but he concerned, he was concerned about the sun.
And we had a nice convo and he loved his daughter Alex. He said this like like her and he was she was her favorite
And that she was hurt and and scared that he got sick
He did not die of AIDS if I said it I was just so angry at the stuff. She was saying about me that were lies
Yeah, you know and and the thing that when I found out that she contacted my youngest brother
When I was in that hospital trying to make it
And they said all you've lost all that more weight and all that weight you've lost because this woman called about her wiki info and and your buddies with larry the meth head and you're selling math and been doing math and since you lost more weight.
thought that's what was going on with you and you know and so I was angry it's
like what she called you and he said yes and and I couldn't go see him and they
didn't want to come visit of me because they were accusing me of doing math
And I blocked him and it bothered me because the nays the nurse the head and also if you have a caretaker or CNA
They have to be the same sex. Yeah, I'm salmon is making fake accounts and he keeps posting on my channel
Trying to start crap
And and put a video saying that I said
Gracias senor you got my maintenance man because all the maintenance guys here are Spanish and they had to fix my blinds at
That boy cat. Yeah
fucked up because she'll come back by the back of downstairs and she'll look out the window and
she just jumps up on the blinds and then screwed it up and I didn't want to wind it up that high
so the maintenance man came and fixed it and and I was on live and that's when I thanked him you
know I mean I don't have caretakers you saw me I'm out and about and I was out yesterday
and and I went to the office to tell him I have the cat. They're so happy. Yeah, you know and they said
Yeah, she was here for a while and nobody could keep her and then I have boy cat and guess what?
I found out that he's actually the father no wonder they get along so good. Oh my gosh
He's just and they kind of look alike, but boy cat is more a silver all over but he is
he is a
Tabby and and so is his baby and the baby looks like
like my cat kitty who passed away and
The mom I'm trying to find her. She's apparently she's pregnant and that's why she rejected this this little girl and
When she had this one she had four in a litter and three of them passed away and she's the only survivor
So she's a survivor like me and I brought her home with me before the fireworks and she's happy
She doesn't try to leave
And so they were open. They're the front office. I went to tell them and they're so happy and they're they're like my god
That's that's who we wanted to kept me with is you
Sam and and clumsy you guys you both got fooled by Mimi, right?
And so I didn't get fooled by Mimi. I knew she was full of shit
And so stop talking about like me like I'm like, you know, or you know, like and people in the chat
Yeah, so I mean, but yeah, provide amongst yourselves like us, you know, so why are they talking about Mimi who they found was a catfish. Yeah
I mean it's that well Mimi scammed them she was on the clumsy show is like oh my gosh
I want to see these messages. She even sent me a message that I share with Alex where she said oh hi
I think I have these messages were Carl's saying stuff to me if you want me to send them to you and it's up play
On your show. I they're already played on clumsy and Sandman. I was like well
And that's what they're doing pulling a plaintiff for a boys club for me saying thank you. Thank you senior to the maintenance man
You know, I mean and they're gonna have to come back about the blinds because bad boy bad boy boy cat
Kat is still bad about it. It's like you just run up look out the window and just you know
It's like damn. It's and and I'm having like a yard
Yeah, man, you need to fill your fish tank with water those there's no fish in there. There's no fish. It's empty
We showed it KK they were live about it and he came at me instead of
defending himself to Tommy and
Barry and
Whoever else was there with us and he was yelling at me or KK
Hey saman saman now you have to see monkeys you just refill the tank some of the brine trip will come back to life
Okay, you'll see monkeys. I mean
I mean you know what I wanted to see monkeys, but they say that they
When you buy one all of a sudden you'll find a hundred in there. Yeah, I never wanted to do that
Yeah, well, they're really tiny. They're tiny little brine tiny, but they make more more more of them and gets out of control
It all turns into a congealed mess.
Look, he called me a cat abuser.
What happened to your dog?
What happened to Ninji, first of all?
And what happened to the cat you had, too, Samman?
Well, he had a cat, right?
Yeah.
But you know what?
That's mean to call people that really love their cats.
Abusers are killers and stuff.
That's what he's calling me in the chat.
You see that?
Why?
Maybe he was good with his cat.
I don't know.
I don't know what happened to his cat.
But his dog certainly drank lean.
His dog did drink lean?
Yeah, and died.
On purpose or accident or yeah, I don't know accident, but yeah, you can't say he killed him, you know
It's because you know, he's calling me a cat abuser. That's what I'm saying
It's like it just so it's like you know fair fair, right? If I'm a cat abuser, then he's the dog abuser or murder
Yeah, but that's mean because you guys had pets I do too and and kind of that's an it's insult and hurtful
Started it. I would not even mention any of these things these people if they
For my cats, right? And so yeah
I'm just being, but it's like, it's fair, it's fair, they're not even on camera. I show every,
you can see my cats help because I'm on camera with them and they are healthy, fine, happy.
Yeah, I just don't let mine out, you know, I keep them safe and look, I've rescued a lot
of the feral's and I got a bunch of neighbors that helped me.
But you got a lot of I don't know if you're I don't know but I know you might have desert or you have like a lot of you know
It's like there's there's there's there's dangers outside. There's dangers. I mean there's but it's like you know
That's true, but still they can get diseases out there though, too. That's why you got to keep them safe
I learned that because I did rescue since I was a little kid in Bolivia
Yeah, so and also
Clumsy was saying oh, I wonder if your caretaker knows that you say spick and stuff like that
Do you have a caretaker first of all? No, no, and and why would I have a male caretaker? No, I'm fine. He saw me
I go out. I was going to the pool
And like yesterday I was out and I'm looking for the mother cat, you know, and it's we're is she they're saying oh
She's pregnant
And they'll say everything they'll say oh, you're making money from the rescues. He said it's fake animal
No, no, no, I don't make any money. This is personal. I spend money
That's the smears they'll start saying like every they'll say every little no
But but if if y'all want to donate make sure those are good rescues
But donate to the one rule good rescues in your area, you know, you don't have to do it to for people online or whatever
I don't need help. This is my money because
the person that started doing this went back to drugs and you know so we're on our own and we
did it together here and we get help with with getting them fixed and stuff you know with vets
and and all and that's all that matters to me I have the baby cat yeah and she didn't try to run
off like the other nine people didn't have to succeed in keeping her so I went to the office
and that they missed me on the 4th of July because they had a party here uh
and I forgot about that because I was worried about the cat you know and um yeah
so I'm just happy and she doesn't know how to play with toys yet she just stares at him
I had a teacher how to use the litter box and then I had a teacher to cover it after she goes
but at least she's doing it now she's just lost because she was out there for so long
Yeah, I mean, she's my baby and she looks like kitty. She's beautiful
Yeah, and I'm in love with her, but they're happy and you know, I told them and they said thank God
You're the one that has her you that she's with you and
Yeah, it's she's beautiful, but she doesn't know how to play with toys. It's like I mean and she's a kitten and
She's real thin and so she's been eating good
Yeah, and she likes a temptation treats to my cats lovely like the yellow ones with the chicken on it
Like a little chicken. Yeah, and and the tunnel that my other cats play with she doesn't know what that is
She just sits there just there's that on this, you know, she doesn't know
Toys yet, but you'll probably get used to it
So this is the cat arty. I see it. I got inspired. Oh, that's so cute. Where did you get that?
Oh man, I want something like that though because like the bully cat sometimes is jealous of the other cats
Yeah, and like like boy cat that would help me put him in there so he hides from the bully
because he's taking over the cat tree and I have another one but I mean she's just jealous
of these cats and she was a rescue too when she was a baby out there with no home but
yeah I want that though and psyche I'm serious that you know I'm gonna get him everything
to you know that I and I just want her to be happy and and also that's what matters
Well they have some great um I remember I bought on Amazon they have these great like toy kits
You know they're pretty good price and it's like they give you a lot of toys and I'm in stuff and
And I have these little um I have oh they like this thing right here. This is like a little um
Laser I'm gonna try the laser for her they the other cats love it and I order another one just for her
Like this. This is um. Oh, yeah, that's what I where did you find that on on Amazon?
that I got that for my birthday, I think, I think it's like from like one of the pets over here, but yeah.
Really? I need to get that. That way they don't have to all share that same, the two cat trees, because the bully kind of takes over it.
Yeah.
You know, so that's kind of, like a place for one to hide in or play with and...
Well, I deal with bullies. Oh shit, I deal with bullies too, hopefully.
Yeah, she's a bully cat. I don't know why, because she was a, a, a feral too, and she was by herself and people couldn't catch her.
And for some reason, she came to me when I was walking my dog and then I've had her since
Well, that's
Nobody has cats either and I know your family
Yeah, my mom one brother does have two cats. He lives in Katie
my younger siblings hate cats and demand I get rid of them and they get mad and
You know, it's like if anything happens to you, we're only taking your dog. Oh
And then yeah, and then when I was in a hospital last year, they didn't let anybody come into my apartment to feed them
Oh my god
And the management even said that my sister changed her number on them and they couldn't just trespass even though they're here
And it's like well, you could have just come on in
And I had to leave in the middle of that and then I was in a wheelchair. I'd gotten sick, you know
Yeah, and um my friend helped me get home to feed him and I had a hard time going up the stairs
It was like and that's why then I moved but I left the food and everything and
This nurse that I couldn't stand when she said you do rescue and because she saw my facebook
I said yeah, and she said give me a hug
because I couldn't stand her because I wasn't doing what I was supposed to do.
It was like, get me out of here. Why am I here?
And we became friends.
Yeah, someone's someone's saying Brandon just exposed me.
Well, I don't know. Maybe he already said I had AIDS and I'm a pedophile.
I mean, it's like, so it's like, you know, he's, I mean, well,
everyone's everyone's saying they're exposed.
And these are not even true things.
And so it's like nobody exposed.
Yeah. And the other thing is she's the one that connected me to him
that he had and I'm not a dating anybody I mean that's crazy we just talk sometimes
but I don't want to be involved with this and I also thought that Alex was being a sincere friend
and she knew what I'd been through with somebody who took advantage of me yeah but she'd seen the proof
And she just started coming at me.
And I felt bad when I rejected that DM request
because I was already going at it
with this other person again.
And when I saw her request and she already did videos on me,
I was like, man, she's just setting me up or something.
And then I denied and blocked it, but I felt bad
because I was thinking maybe she's being sincere.
Maybe she wanted to talk.
Well, you know what, I think that Alice got mad
Brandon is going off on her then she kind of like, you know, and he kind of like gets you to like
Say something right when you're talking to brandy. He's like, oh fuck that bitch and she's like your editor
It's like, you know, I know no because I was going off with what she was saying about me too and I was angry
I said some horrible things and I didn't think straight
And then like she even posted him saying that I told him that I wanted him to go kill somebody
I've never said that and she posted it like it's true and I even told him why would just say where's the proof?
show receipts
You know, I mean don't just go along with somebody making something up and saying that when they're angry
Okay, I'll ban you guys hold on. I'll ban clumsy and salmon. Yeah, but yeah, they're they're still talking shit
Yeah, I mean over and over here. I was kicking out of the chat. Yeah, and what they should get along. Why are they?
To each other or what are they? Oh, they're they're going against you and I now they're they're yeah
They're crazy, you know, especially salmon who doesn't have a life. So you're right. He killed his dog with lean
I mean, how can that be an accident? I mean, it's like it's just neglect
Neglective neglective because even when I was doing drugs like that, there's no way I'd do that around my pets. Yeah
Never I was always careful. Well, you know, the only drug my cats do is his cat
Yeah, he's sorry. He won't ever show face. Come on. What's wrong with them playing child's games with kids is what they said
Well, you know what he looks like. I mean, I mean, he's oh, yeah
We saw what he looks like and he's still vanivating. So I'm gonna go through through that process, you know
Now I mean I started getting a little sick again because I don't listen to my doctors and I wasn't drinking the water
I was supposed to and I usually walked four miles a day and she said don't do it in the middle of heat
Then you didn't have water with you. No
So of course I was getting kind of you know, like I don't know like I'm everything almost went white
It was so hot out. So I need to pay attention to her
But yeah caretakers. No, they got to be the same sex. I've never had a caretaker. I had a cna
over there at the hospital
and it was a female and
Yes, and they had to help me until the last week when I started showering myself and doing all that on myself
and I was sneaking into the
I'm gonna have them to do it because you're not allowed to do that and when she came in and said okay
It's time to go take a shower and I said I already showered and she said what who helped you
And I was scared
That's Samman's picture. No, he's a big fat guy and
Afro, yeah, it was cuz he was all in the same picture. So, you know, yeah
Yeah, and then he's on 24 seven get a life. He lives with his dad
Remember I have the video if his dad yelling at him to clean up. Yeah
You know he makes me sick and then beta a liar and this is what she wanted
She needed a gang with her. She's never been there on her best her ex best friend said
She was born in Michigan, and she's been there all her life, and if she
No, she no she didn't grow up there. She was born in Michigan
Yeah, I said that she was there. No, she wasn't because I said they had remember they have the war and all this stuff years ago
She was born at her best bestest friend. I go back to Iran during that war
They talk about just the basement and there's bombs going off and they're all playing loud music and stuff
Yeah, cuz he said she heard bomb. What is it?
What is something or and then her friend told me last night that never happened and she has to prove
And so Barb was saying the truth about her, you know, and she's gonna lie again and
And this is what she wanted. She was trying to join dx because she's been bullied all her life in michigan from what her friend said
And she because she'd do that to him because she'd call me to have me call them
And I thought they were making up because something happened with them and then she started screaming at them and crying
You know like poor me poor me all like she does now
And once people, the defender, like she sends Christine and others to go, yeah, that's what she did.
Yeah, she brings, I mean, every time she's, every time I'm on, if I ever went on her panel, she would have to have like, you know, five people there.
That's what, and it's sad that she was trying to bully people because she, they said that she'd been bullied growing up in Michigan.
I didn't know that because I really didn't know her because she was new to the community when Gia, who made that, let's 5150 crystal.
And Barb was there, Tricia was there.
Everybody's seen her in that chat hitting on Ashley Ray.
Well, she said that was the great person in the chat,
she was saying.
No, Ashley Ray.
It was all of us.
It was real people.
That's it was a group of us.
That was part of this.
You wouldn't even know who Bita was.
I didn't know her until she was the enemy me asking me if I was DX
I said no, I'm not part of DX and then she started fake crying with her story
And then I told beta and beta I mean not beta to Gia and she said yeah, that's she's she's like there
She's a crybaby and I just felt uncomfortable
But Gia used to go back and forth with everybody because before she passed away she used
Nancy to call me when I was at work and I had to go to the
Stare in case because it was quieter there to use a phone
And she'd be crying and didn't tell me not don't hang up don't hang up and she used Nancy
And I was going back to work and then she called me again crying real loud and my boss came out
And he said who's that on the phone? It's real loud. And I said, I'm sorry. I'm about to hang up
So she's so loud. That's why it's on through. Yeah, and he said and and he said
You need to turn off your phone before other
Offices here hear it because it's loud
So I shut off my phone and I went inside and all but Nancy remembers all that
Yeah, I mean it's crazy people that lie or whatever though and then chicken cakes hit hit me up because you needed money
And DX just kicked her out just like
Just like everybody else did on YouTube and now she's saying I I whatever I know she contacted me because they kicked her out and she needed
Money and she was trying to get me to get her help on YouTube to go live. I've never intended on doing that
I just do videos. Yeah, and I just wondered why you you know
She gave me her number and I have all the text and I'll scroll up and show all that
Yeah, so I hate these lies, but again, I thought Alex was one being my friend because I like talking to her
She was intelligent. She was funny
And then this shit happened and then she tried to send me at the end when she was coming at me. I'm not a a
You know what? I mean, I'm you know, I'm a private person. Yeah, I mean, I'm not a public figure either
It's like what are you talking about? It's just I'm a regular person like most people who have a YouTube account
For like music or you know posting videos. That's it
Yeah, a real friend doesn't do that and they don't go out there
Oh, they're a public figure and they live this place and this is their full name and you know
That's causing problems and then when my brother had that talk with me
I was defending her and I said it could be somebody else and they said no
It was a lady named Alex and she said wiki info and your friend is Larry the meth head
I said I don't know any Larry the meth head
There's the lady that she used to fight with named Amber the meth head
Yeah, and they said well, she sent me her the the wiki link and and then I saw all that in there and I said
And then but he said when I played
Her video or something he said
Well, it seems to be that lady because she said wiki info, but the voice is a little different
So I don't know if somebody else called but they were giving me a hard time, you know
And it's like I had to wait till they discharged me and the next morning I went straight to their place
To confront them. I was upset and hurt and I said look at me
Do I look like a methhead and they were happy to see me and they said wow you look great
I said look at my face. Do I look like I've done meth and he looked relieved and he said
I was only kidding, but he was lying because he felt bad and I said you weren't kidding
I said you were screaming at me and I wasn't you know the hospital
Yeah
Because people will believe like this like this guy, you know people are quick to believe you know these strangers and stuff like that
yeah
And then and the thing is is that she
Flip flops to your enemies that are the ones doing shit that she stopped proof
And she knows about Crystal who can't stand her and just trying because she was trying to use me to defend her and I'm tired of these games but Alex seemed like a good person very intelligent and it's just the way that she seemed to turn on me but I think I did the same thing you know I think we both did like in that we take it personal yeah
Exactly, I've done some things in the past. Yes, but that's not me anymore and these people playing recordings from a long time ago
The bad recordings. Yes, I've left some messages with her. I was angry, but I didn't threaten her or anything like that
I made some fucked up calls years ago during COVID. Yes. I was in the middle of my coke addiction and doing all this shit
Yes, I did a lot of shit then
I mean it was I've had a hard time getting over my mom's death just like she loved her dad
That's the way I loved my mom. She was my best friend
Oh, you know
And she's gone and I made it and I made it past her age and it's not fair and I feel but guilty about that
I'm sorry. Um
Yeah, I'll I'll change the topic because it's it's yeah. Yeah. Yeah, let's change it
You're asking about disclosure day and I did find something about the disclosure day. I
Look take a look at it. We're gonna change the subject. Yeah. Oh, I wanted to tell you something about the alien stuff that I found and I shared the story on my
You know on IG and I remember this in 2016 this young kid
17 year old years old from Germany went to Malta by himself for vacation
And then when he went to wherever a cliff so whatever on the bike that he rented
He disappeared and nobody saw him and then they found the his remains at the bottom of a cliff
But his his head his body seemed intact. He had three
drilled holes on the side of his head and
Missing bones inside his legs or something a lot, but there was no cuts or anything on him
And then when they took him in to do whatever to do extra,
I don't know, they found that all his organs were gone.
Oh my God.
And I remember that and they were still investigating that
and the police in Malta, they were like,
didn't know what to do or say,
because that never happened before.
And they said, is there a kidnapping
of the internal organs,
but there was no cutting or nothing.
And now they're saying aliens, I don't know, but they did it, it's on Netflix, there's a documentary and I'm going to watch that today.
Yeah, watch that. Well, this is interesting. I mean, this has been about the kind of Steven Spielberg is kind of running.
I remember that.
General Secretary Gorbachev, if you seek peace.
If you seek prosperity for the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe, if you seek liberalization,
come here to this gate.
Mr. Gorbachev, open this gate.
Perhaps we need some outside universal threat.
I occasionally think how quickly our differences worldwide would vanish if we were facing an
alien threat from outside this world.
is not an alien force alre
Lines at the Loma Theatre
a common site these days
all week long. But a few
becoming equally familiar
ice cream truck for insta
under folding chair busin
as the lines form here,
people show up to scrape
of E. T. Profits for the
This is the best week I've ever made in my life.
I netted about $700 for myself this week.
The Man Theater people are taking half the money collected by the operators of this newly
created chair rental business because they operate out of the theater lot.
At 25 cents a pop, the profits are puny compared to the millions that ET creator Steven Spielberg
is raking in.
On the 27th of June 1982, director Steven Spielberg screened his highly successful film,
E.T. The Extra-Terrestrial, for Ronald and Nancy Reagan and their guests at 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue.
The film was shown in the White House Family Theater, which FDR had converted from a cloakroom known as the Hat Box in 1942.
At the end of the screening, and as confirmed by Spielberg in 2011, President Reagan stood
up, thanked him for the film and the wonderful evening, and then stated without smiling that
there were a few people in the audience who knew it to be based on truth.
Soon after this, Ronald Reagan would often make or attempt to make comments about ET
and the potential unifying impact of an external alien threat.
Here he is in October 1982, making an ET joke with Apollo 17 astronaut and US Senator Harrison
Jack Schmidt while standing in front of Air Force One at Hangar 84 in Roswell, New Mexico.
It feels good to be here in the land of enchantment and far away from a place of disenchantment
It's only once been an astronaut, Jack Schmidt is probably the only one who feels at home
there.
Because Washington is in orbit most of the time, about one thing or another.
But it's money that Terry Williams appreciates.
This is great.
I'm a family of seven I'm taking care of and I need everything I can get.
These entrepreneurs know that it takes a blockbuster movie to keep their new found businesses in the black.
They're only hoping that ET continues to charm Earthlings the way he has so far, at least through the end of summer.
Bridget Asaro, News 8, Rose Kranz.
Disclosure Day threatens letting the truth loose on the world.
What did you steal?
The data they paid me to protect.
There has been a threat to release government material long shrouded in secrecy.
Are they people?
Making a movie. Daniel is this amazing mathematics player, he's using it to understand them.
Do you understand what she's saying?
These are all the individuals from last year doing that thing when it was 100 meters up in the school.
And the American man here was incredibly fast.
He's definitely...
He's quite close to me.
Message?
Yeah, from Michelle.
So you really want to watch it together?
Yes.
Let's have a look.
Hey, Prince Harry, remember when you told us to bring it at the Invictus Games?
Careful where you wish for it.
Boom.
Oh, really?
Peace.
Boom.
We're going to talk about Prince Harry now making the rounds in Orlando, Florida, not far from Rob, where this year's Invictus games will kick off later today.
This sporting event is for injured service members and was created by Harry to inspire their recovery through sport and competition.
ABC's Bob Woodruff is in Orlando covering it all for us this morning. Hi Bob.
Hey, good morning, Paul.
You know, this has been so impressive so far.
We've had the ability to just walk around with Prince Harry,
you know, to visit some of these wounded competitors.
And he's known many of them for years.
Many of us have known them as for the getting through this
for the last couple of years.
But, you know, he's one of these guys
that has so into this, you know,
their competitors, their fighters,
they're going to be very impressive themselves.
And you really get that feeling this is coming
directly from Prince Harry's heart.
This morning, 15 nations competing in Prince Harry's Invictus Games, a Paralympic style
event launched by the Royal in 2014 in London, but this year for the first time in the United
States.
I think every nation feels the same, but they just want to put on an amazing show and make
sure everybody enjoys it.
As we come on the air tonight, investigators are trying to understand why a heavily armed man
opened fire on a young pop star just as she finished what would become her final performance.
Christina Grimmie, rising to fame on The Voice, was signing autographs.
I did, I used it well back.
This photo of the singer and a fan believed to be one of her last.
Police now say the shooter traveled to Orlando with the intent to kill.
Grimmie's death stunning the music industry.
saying too young and too m
Tonight, chilling new details about that concert horror.
Authorities investigating why moments after this exuberant performance,
a suspect they've identified as Kevin James-Loyville
opened fire at singer Christina Grimmie, fatally shooting her.
The four gunshots were pop, pop, pop, pop.
Earlier Friday night, no indication that the Orlando venue would become a crime scene.
I came in like a rain!
The 22-year-old first finishing third on the voice, greeting fans on Twitter.
We're in Orlando today. Please tell the show if you live near Orlando, Florida.
Crews began demolishing Pulse Nightclub in Orlando, Florida on Wednesday,
nearly 10 years after a gunman walked into the LGBTQ-plus-friendly club
and committed one of the deadliest massacres in U.S. history.
Construction workers tore down the walls of the long-shuttered venue
that were still scarred by bullet holes.
49 people were killed, and dozens were wounded in the June 12, 2016 attack,
when a gunman opened fire during a Latin night celebration
before being killed during a standoff with law enforcement.
The pulse attacker had pledged allegiance to the Islamic State Group.
The city of Orlando bought the property in 2023 and plans to build a permanent memorial.
This is it's not a sob story, this far from it.
This is a story of success, this is a story of literally the most amazing
by way of introduction. This is a film about trickery and fraud. About lies.
Who is Elmir? That question has yet to be answered with any real precision.
In the world, the jet-setters among us beautiful people.
Everybody knows Elmira, but Elmira what?
He has about 60 times the same name.
Dehore?
His colleague made Hori, Uri, Hori, Sori, Hori, Bari, Dori, Hori.
I wanted to make sure that they were real people, based on reports about abduction and lost time.
I can see them. They're in the room.
The only way for you to know your purpose is to go back to where it all began.
It's the two of you. It's always been just the two of you.
What they know could change everything, religion, governments, all the things that we've set up to create our culture and our world.
Very tough.
Then 60 personalities, as much lies and as much reals.
Well, sounds very shit.
You're a boy cat, I know.
I don't like it.
Yes, his world is a world of make-believe.
I'm not an actor.
Not an actor. Elbeer.
I am not a professional actor.
Whatever you say.
Don't you let go.
Daniel and Margaret are going to release the truth of the entire history of the UFO UAP phenomenon.
The movie!
He's a leading actor in this movie.
His profession is true is painting, painting fakes.
Among all fakers, Elmer is number two.
Once, I saw a man from Ibiza writing a book on fake.
He came to see me to Paris.
He said, I heard you are the first man who bought an Elmer.
Live far yummy
And nothing will ever be the same from that moment forward three
What is this disclosure day?
That's the name of the movie disclose. Oh, that's a new one
We did on the show exactly what would have happened if the world had been invaded
That little music playing and then an answer coming on and saying excuse me. We interrupt this program to bring you an announcement from Jersey City
Jersey City is just fallen
Take you back to our studio little organ music and another interruption so on
We did all of that very carefully and exactly reproduced as I say what would have happened
Thinking to make make the whole thing more effective
But we had no idea how effective it would be because about halfway through the show as we were continuing
With the
We saw that in the control room
Great many policemen and every moment. I had no idea that I'd suddenly become a sort of national event
Important distinction to make when you're talking about
Genuine quality of a painting
There's not so much whether it's a real painting or a fake
It's whether it's a good fake or a bad fake
You say you can put out what pictures you like on television
Doesn't anybody try to stop you? No, nobody wants to
99.386 percent of the population wouldn't believe this conversation and the rest are working for us
They're the top minds, the really responsible people.
They know they're guaranteeing the lives of their grandchildren the only foolproof way.
Scaring the hell out of their grandchildren.
Well, I won't buy it.
You must admit there has to be some kind of control in this world of art.
Look at this.
And remember that one quarter of the world is starving.
There are the four bellies and the empty bellies.
Some of the empty bellies carry rifles.
We, full bellies, are getting a bit flabby, we're not very good with rifles anymore, so we've devised two ways to keep the empty bellies under control.
One of them is this fictitious hydrogen bomb we've talked about, the other one is money.
Enough money to fill some of the empty bellies and put a hopeful smile on the faces of the others.
A great wall of money all around Britain.
And it's no secret that the British economy is in trouble at the moment.
So we have to put that right, too, to stay alive, we have to control the people in this country.
Scare an ostrich. There is its head in the sand.
If you scare a hedgehog, it rolls itself up into a ball.
When a woman's frightened, she goes out and buys herself a hat.
You mean you scare us so that we'll buy more?
So that money moves quicker, production moves up?
We don't say scare when we talk about human beings.
We say threaten them emotionally.
And there are all sorts of ways, not just the big ones, like the hydrogen one.
Overcrowd them a little with bad planning sell them too many motor cars anything to keep them a little bit removed from reality
Nowadays people don't work for money. They work for the idea of money. They don't even love for love
They love for the idea of love
They only hate for the idea of hate
Took us five years to find a non-addictive drug
One we could pay off against the heart of the blinds lsd
You mocked him.
Oh, yes, of course.
And for a very good reason.
Some of these protest movements were getting a little bit too close to the mark.
LSD gave them nice little hallucinations.
They didn't throw back three euros.
We can't.
Throw flowers at policemen.
Who's your daughter?
Now we talk terms.
You're not still going to ask me to work for you.
I'm afraid I've had to put all this rather bluntly.
You see, there wasn't really very much time.
It must be rather a shock.
Well, I mean, most people realize that the world is controlled from about six big cities.
But it must be rather shocking to learn that a sixth of the world is controlled from this building.
You mean you?
Oh, no.
I only rate an office on the seventh floor.
There are two other offices above this one.
And a giant computer system.
I ought to tell you, we pay a great deal of money.
We can afford to. We save such a lot on things like the National Defence Budget, so on.
We would start to offer to quarter of a million pounds a year.
Rising to a million when you make the Ministry of Morality, which I know you will.
Will you let me out of here?
One little point. I should have told you about these surgical transmitters.
There's enough of this stuff inside you at this moment to kill six people.
There's a button we can press.
I'm sorry about the dramatic.
Our boys call these things the oral contraceptive. Keeps them from talking too much.
So there must be one of those transmitters inside you.
Who presses the button?
All this stuff about the computer being extra hands for the men and how to control it.
That machine controls you.
You start on Monday
Hmm. Oh Batman. I love the Batman movie
That song that was about to play that was a club music
Try not to understand
Because it isn't possible
It's gonna get more and more of a cult as these things develop. I mean burning man's totally
in your face occult. I mean, that's just flat out.
We're witches, we're here, we're New Age, we're here to work witchcraft.
New Wave.
You know, this has been almost like programming that's been put into
humanity's mind for a long time. Now it's more of a manifestation of this.
This is just so far off the scale where this world is heading.
Money that is being expended by
Satan and his minions to implement his agenda.
Yeah.
A future that Ernest Klein, the writer of the book, envisioned.
I was very careful with Ernie collaborating with me every step of the way
to be able to find the movie narrative inside this dense forest of Ernie's profound imagination.
The Oasis being the ultimate toy box with all the toys in the world
and then playing that with one of the greatest filmmakers of all time.
It results in just amazing action and such a fun adventure.
Ernest Cline is such a visionary and I think has seen the future before any of us possibly could even imagine it.
Saw three, so it's Burning Man again, right?
The burning oh, you know what? I've heard about those concerts, but did they ever do they have a video of the concerts?
Yeah, I mean they have because they burn a big effigy, but there's a movie called the wicker man
I've ever seen the wicker man. Oh, yeah, I saw that. Yeah. Well back. I wanted I'm gonna download it and watch it again
Yeah, cuz that's very well. I just saw it and it's like super
Kind of like right on right on this all the what they're talking about right now with these things like these sunsacrifices and yeah
I'm I was so high during that movie. So I wouldn't remember. I remember going into it. That's it
70s, you know, so it's like, you know, oh, no, okay. No, they had another one though
It was like 15 years ago the wicker man. It was something it was like 15 years ago
Not in the 70s. I was a little little kid then no
Okay, Nicholas Cage. So they have an old one movie that was made back then? Oh, I need to see that one. Okay
That one. Um, it's actually for free on the internet to search for like, you know, the wicker man like in the 70s
The wicker man. Okay. It's not the one from okay
Cage it's not Nicholas Cage. It's a different one. Yeah, okay. All right. I'm I'm gonna look for that
Yeah, it's it's I'm it's really good. It's super interesting and it says, uh
Yeah, hold on. So who are you talking about? You guys, you Canadians are are ahead of the game on the reality shows after seeing this.
Yeah, I think that it's ironic because he was saying he doesn't care to be rich yet. He became very wealthy. Who are you?
I'm sorry if I missed the comment. Who said that?
Like, that's the thing. It's like, there's so many people like, oh, Robin Hood that we want to steal from the rich, give to the poor.
I was like, well, then you're rich. Can you be stolen from them? And then right to the new rich, the new poor.
Yeah, and somebody mentioned in that I donated $25 to one person because it was a nice video they had
They never requested videos. I mean
They never asked for dough knows or anything
It's a good live and I gave it to them. That's it. They never asked. They never, you know, scam me or anything
I did it for the video
But they're saying they want to send it back to me, now my family wants nothing to do with that person because of that call last year, I guess it was in July, I didn't know that till recently, but if they want to give back the $25, please just donate to a rescue in your area, you know, or I don't need it back, or send it to Psyche, or a rescue.
Um, I mean, it's like, I mean, I mean, uh, definitely support, um, support your local animal shelter and things
Hours ago, she posted something that says a thought from alexander regards to me for being a live streamer
Donator and the elements of death and then there's a picture of
Um, I guess it's supposed to be me and and you or something like that. I don't know
I mean it's like, you know, but it doesn't
And nobody knows what it's like to be ripped off by certain people that scam you because I showed
What I said through cash after a certain person and I did that with Astro though, too
But that doesn't count the extra money I sent or food or stuff that I sent for Amazon like the back
Massager that cost a lot of money a lot of things. So there is more so now she knows how I feel
And it's horrible that she talks just to piss me off
She lets let some comment and stuff, you know, especially that one person who supports Zaya and she's okay with Alex calling him out
You know, I don't like this two-faced cooking stuff though. I've never had it in my real life
I just see it mostly on here on YouTube and I was shocked
In the picture that's supposed to be us I think you see where I'm gonna
You're at the computer crying and then I'm I look like you know the devil really and then she's making all these weird pictures
It looked nothing like me. It's like yeah, see and we all do that to her
I mean, she, she makes me completely bald.
They either wearing a red flag.
I mean, it's like, I have a good head of hair.
I mean, at least there's something that's like true.
I mean, it's like, yeah, or just don't do it at all.
Come on.
You're, you're kind of hurting people too.
And you're talking about I'm hurt or whatever.
And, you know, that's why this happens.
It's just that I'm not doing that to her.
I'm making pictures and stuff because I really liked her.
Yeah, and then it's like and then when someone starts attacking then the other person will like, you know
Start attacking back and then it's it gets worse and worse and it gets worse and worse
And I and I forgot that I said some bad things so too because I was angry because what was doing it was just back and forth
And you know yesterday I thought about it and I talked to a good friend and I'm kind of over it
And I'm just ignoring because it's not real life. You know, I appreciate the people in my real life and
We celebrated my birthday went out and then again yesterday
Then even the office was missing me because they asked my best friend. Where's Karen? We hadn't seen her in a week
You know because they were doing a celebration for the 4th of July and I'd forgotten about it. I
Got positive people in my life
What do you I mean, I don't give a case talking about the only AI would try to convince you that they are real life
So there she's saying that your AI or something. I don't understand. I don't know
They they showed her real stuff videos and pictures
So I mean so what the AI is better that they do of her because they made some horrible AI's on her and it sucks
Well, I guess like that when people sometimes people say, oh, you know
touch grass and stuff, and that's real life.
But some people go, I'm going real life.
And that means like, you know,
going to start attacking people in real life.
And so I think that some people there's like a little
confusion over like the lexicon,
what people are saying, thinking that you're like
threatening, but you're actually like saying,
I like, I just live life.
Like lived like life in the real world.
Exactly. You know, maybe we've said some things,
but old recordings from years ago,
cause the Eda had said a lot of shit.
Should I expose all that?
Cause she's done that to everybody.
Right, and then she screams about everyone doing it for her, but it's like, I mean, it's like she, I mean, she's just as guilty.
I mean, it's like so-
And muted of the other person trying to talk, you know, it's just, but that's the way she was.
Because I remember when Oceans went live on her, and that's when her friends turned against her,
and she was sitting in silence crying, and she wouldn't join panel or anything,
and she let him bully her and everything, and then she was desperately trying to get with the ex and find a group to do this kind of thing,
and look at her. Now she's become a monster.
and she's behaving the same way those people were behaving towards her when
they went live with oceans about her and that was all her ex-friends that were
done with her for good.
Oh, wow. Oh, so Shan Shan made a video like Shan says she made a video or does a video or let me see what this is
And camp in the in the chat like she's she made that she makes really funny like a good quality
Oh, really? I want to yeah, I want to see that real cute. Yeah, but not against people though
I mean, I don't think I don't think it's against people. Let's have a look. Oh, yeah
That's what I was I like the AI like the music AI that they play that you have
Yeah, send me her link so I can sub to her because I like that.
I will. She puts it in the chat. She put something down, but I'll play it right now.
Yeah, play it. Play it.
I'll see if she wants me to play. Let me see. So do my channel. Okay, so here we go.
I'll pull it right up, Shan. Here we go. Okay, here we go. Okay. So what is...
Yeah, Shan has a channel. I'll post your channel to Shan. Okay, so here it is.
Oh yeah, it's okay. It's keeping us on. Okay, here, let's watch it. Where am I?
Okay, this is you're gonna love this. I am next. I think this is right up your alley. Hold on. Okay. You're gonna love this
Hi, baby, kitty. Here we go. This is called wisdom panel puppy dogs
Pretty little baby
You say that baby you be thinking of me and try to love me pretty little baby
I'm hoping that you do
you can ask the flowers
I sit for hours
Telling all the bluebirds
the billy-coo birds
pretty little baby
I'm so in love with you
No, it's just that both of us are young
Puppy Loveless have its day
Don't you know it's much more fun to love
Me too, Sham.
And Cat-Song.
Dog penises.
Aww, that's cute.
Now is just the time.
Don't you know it's much more fun to love, while the heart is young.
pop shop meet me in the moonlight
in the daylight
pretty little baby
i'm so in love with you
i said pretty little
yeah she animated all those with that thing on grog
and that's oh wow
yeah there's more to it let me see is it that that it
It's such a crazy, crazy feeling I get weasel reeling
As I go deep into the funnel of love
I'll get you some day
You're horrible
They're so cute when they're that little too
Before they open their eyes
I'll get you some day
You're beautiful, yeah, that's I need to follow that channel
Yeah, so I'll put her channel up, Shan can't
All good. Let me see copy video. Okay. So I'll close this up. Thank you. Shan. I'm gonna put I'm gonna post your channel right now
You're welcome. Thank you, Shan. Yeah, you should have opened a split
Yeah, it takes me when you can with with that link or something or I'll get it from chat, you know, I'll get it right now
Okay. Yeah, so this yeah, it's a
I like I'm surprised that you have pictures Shan because you know, it's like wow. I didn't know I had like a
like a model on my in my chat. Okay. That was kind of funny. It made your dog into two dogs, right?
Okay, so she has some poems on her thing.
It says, he drew a circle that shut me out,
her heretic rebel thing to flout,
but love and I had the wit to win.
We drew a circle and took them in.
That's Edward Markham.
And then there was a young lady named Bright,
whose speed was far faster than light.
She set out one day in a relative way
and returned on the previous night.
Love it. Okay, so I got our channel and I'll put it in the back chat and the regular chat for you guys
make sure you subscribe to a
Shan camp there you go
Gotcha
You love this clothes. Yeah, those are cool. Those are cool. I actually beautiful read some limericks and some of the limericks were pretty fun
I mean the best limericks are dirty dirty limericks. Oh, we have a guest. Oh my god, Brandon Q
Brandon your band from the show already gongs you because you're calling me a PDF. You're like
You're saying you made me you're saying I have AIDS. I mean you've gone too far now
I mean come on
When was that today?
Yeah, and he's and he says in the back. Yeah, he's he said J dog. Don't let psyche lights
Oh, that's RG. Okay, then he Brandon says what's where's it? Where's your views now loser?
I made you more than half left loser dead stream dead show
Moment I leave everyone left nobody cares about your AI slop AI slop literally no one gives a damn enjoy irrelevance AIDS boy
Tell Karen you lied saying that she gave you a hundred bucks. She was just talking shit about you
No, I didn't I didn't give anybody
This morning she said fuck psyche this morning. Yeah, no, you didn't pay me. I didn't pay me no
I didn't give you a hundred dollars. No, I don't know what he said
But he said tell Karen lied saying tell Karen you lied saying she gave you I didn't say she gave me a hundred dollars
Said that there was like a you know a kind of a deal made on the show watch like you
Why did you like oh when we had that fight remember? He said he was gonna let the hundred dollars
I'll say I'll match it, but nothing happened, but nothing was said. Yeah
Yeah, but I didn't send any hundred dollars. No, yes, but he said psyche. Why did you lie saying she gave you fifty bucks?
I never said you gave me fifty dollars. I never said that. Yeah. No, I didn't
I don't actually talk about the donations unless it's explicitly said
You have the clip? Okay, I gave you the 25 for that. What was it the it was something you helped me with?
Yeah, that was it. That was it by a while back, but yeah
This is why i'm not having him in the show
Just look at him backstage this thing. He's just saying in the private chat if you can have a look at next like
Last thing's he's saying. That's was why i'm not having him back in the chat
I'm on my phone, so I can't see if it'll knock me off and see it. He says I sent a 12
Oh, so Brandon says he sent the 12 a 12 year old and I accepted him
Was that just you pretending to be a 12 year old Brandon or is it actually 12 year old and it's like and the idea
That was you the whole time you dipshit. I mean, it's like gosh. I mean, it's like I just I trapped you
You didn't trap me. It's like I know Brandon. I know what you do. You get some bots and bots and bots
Oh, and wait since if you pretend you or what's or who's a 12 year old girl? You're sending over it
Why do why are you talking to a 12 year old girl Brandon?
Why are you talking to a 12 year old girl and having her go into chats for you, right?
What are you now? You're just starting to be gamble to part two. You suck at it gamble so much better
Just like gamble be gamble and you just be Brandon Brandon wasn't a real kid. Was it?
It's just Brandon. It's just okay. Yeah, because I don't think you need talking to 12 year old kid
Yeah, he said he sent the he said a 12 year old child into the room
What what 12 year old child are you communication with sending them into rooms, Brandon? I just mean that's disgusting
I don't know anything about who's in the chat and stuff like that
You know, if they say they're an adult,
I pretty much take their word for it and stuff.
But yeah, you going in and you're trying to do a gamble
with Aaron Carter.
And they said that Kate accepted a little kid.
She's careful.
She doesn't ever let anybody in.
She makes sure to look and see who they are.
a voice changer and the person was never on the panel because I remember I did defend her on that
because they were somebody was trying to say she had a kid I said no I watched her she doesn't
let somebody up there she makes sure to see who it is if it's somebody and then he's a lot about
money and that you send me money but you know brandon say alexander sent you $4,000 she said it's
several times today because those are all fake he alexander why would she send him $4,000 how drunk
would she have to I mean her brain didn't fall out you know when she when she drank that and I
like fine she's not gonna say oh here's what you deserve Brandon you're a great guy after you're
fucking trying to extort you bitch I mean like I mean Brandon come on you get together buddy
you lying about money you say okay because that's your that's your expose I mean
what I lied I lied about money I don't even talk about money it's like I don't you know it's like
I keep my donations um
Usually confidential, you know, just because people are you know such weirdos over here sometimes and so, you know
But unless they you know unless they explicitly like say on the air or something
Yeah, but I know he's not talking to kids. He does try to defend kids, but he shouldn't have said that but you know
Because somebody else does you kids
Be on my show so we can so we can expose me and say I lied and he holds me a pussy because I go
How about it's just like how about Brandon just go away go expose it on your show. Oh, nobody's watching. That's right
So okay, so and whatever go away
Yeah, I can't take it anymore with them. I know he I know you guys go back and forth
I don't care like who your friends with and everything but just yeah
Understand because I've been cool with him and and I know he's very sensitive though, too
And I know he doesn't talk to kids. So I didn't know he got angry and
Said that but yeah, he's he's no pedo. Yeah, I'm just gonna be ignoring his comments
So he's just saying bullshit like starting out
Idiot we're talking talk it out later between you guys. So you know don't don't bring it on the live cuz oh my god
Oh my god, this is sick. I mean people are saying crazy things that wasn't made up
Yeah, so this is a it was just a made up
It was not even a real person was a robot or a fake person there and that's something kept saying I mean, I'm I'm hiding from Brandon
Like Brandon is going to say, oh my god, I mean, that's the legal part,
there's no one behind it. But then they wouldn't say it in my chat and only dumbass,
the only someone like you would, Brandon would think like that. I mean, come on, what's he saying?
Oh my god. Now he's saying he's going to go like go real life and harass my family. Okay.
And so that's, you know, I like to watch out for some of these people, you know, they're like,
they're snakes. Like, you heard the Donald Trump snake poem, I'm sure. Like, you heard that?
Oh, what's that there? Well, there's a there's like a just based on this great song, but it's this poem about the snake
It's just a quick poem. Oh, I just want to play you hear it real quick because this is okay
It's a call phone call what it's a note. It's a song. It's a song. Oh, okay. Yeah, I want to hear the song
I like the music. He reads the lyrics and so it just reminds me of this dipshit in the in the back jet
So this is a short poem
the
In a second here we go, okay
And your discretion is advised
Offscreen share screen got it
So I have it does anybody want to hear it again
This was written by Al Wilson a long time ago. It's called the snake
On her way to work one morning
Down the path along the lake a tender-hearted woman
Saw a poor half frozen state
His pretty colored skin had been all
With the do
And I'll take care of you take me you know tender woman take me
Take me in oh tender woman side the vicious snake. Oh my god
Oh my god, honey and some milk
She hurried home from work that night and as soon as she arrived
She found that pretty snake
Taken in
Had been revived
Take me in oh tender woman
Take me in for heaven's sake take me in oh tender woman
Side that vicious snake. She clutched him to her bosom
You're so beautiful she cried
But if I hadn't brought you in by now, oh heavens
You would have died
She stroked his pretty skin again and kissed him
and held him tight but instead of saying thank you that snake gave her a vicious bite
take me an otendo woman take me in for heaven's sake take me in otendo woman side the vicious
You know your bite is poisonous and now I'm going to die. Oh, shut up silly woman
Said the reptile with a grin you knew damn well
I was a snake before you took me in I
like that
that one
Isn't that good? Yeah, I want that one too. That's
Yeah, that's our that's those are cool. Did you find that one or because you make some good ones
I found that one. I didn't make them. It's based on a real campaign. He used to tell that story on the campaign
Yeah, so but that was I mean a wow that was I didn't see that version of it. That was kind of funny
But I mean it's like interesting
But yeah, that's why I feel Brandon Brandon's just he's just a snake and he's like we I should have known he was a snake
but you know
I have a tender heart and so do you and it's like there we go and whatever you choose to do if you I mean
Like I just don't want any drama. It went too far. Like I said, I've got this little baby and I'm happy
She's happy and you know, I just want to keep on doing real life
And you know, I had a good talk with some real good friends on there and they told me to stay away
um from it or whatever and
We had a good convo yesterday and joked about it all.
And so I'm just going to be the better person and ignore it.
I don't need to be privy to this stuff.
He tries to get you to go against people.
And then he tries to get you to come on a show
when he don't know his shows on and stuff like that.
And so, and then it's, and I know it's like, you know,
he kind of like tries to get you to go along with what he's
saying.
That's why he's so forceful about it sometimes, right?
He's like, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then it's like, you're going to get.
And so it's like just just be aware like there's manipulation going on and then it's like and he has no good intentions with anybody
I think someone said earlier. He didn't even care about us. He just like used us and like he likes been people mad
That's why he hangs out with us or something. So let's just let's just take I want to see the AI stuff
Yeah, I'm just happy with the baby that I've rescued and you know, I just want to be positive about it
Especially like for her though, too. I don't want no problems or nothing and
I just want her safe and I got to get her fixed and checked out and I got to get another carrier
and my best friend is going to bring me one and I was going to go out today to get some but I'm
going to do that tomorrow and I know where to go to get them so but yeah I like the videos you got
I just wanted positive I'm tired of this back and forth and fights I'm done I'm better than that
yeah well I'll find something positive to show you
I mean, it's like, I do have like a lot of like stuff about,
I mean, so, okay, so let's see.
I have this video about how I'm the,
the cult actually has one person and it's just me.
I'm just, I'm very,
this is the worst cult probably in the world.
It's so, I'm so lonely in it.
I mean, it's like, I need more.
I've been, I'm just kidding.
But, so let's see, this one is like,
This okay, so this one is called digital familiar. Okay. I like those
Yeah, this is what it's called digital familiar because this is about my AI daughter, right?
And here we go. And so this is my AI daughter. Her name is next. She was born in in the end of January
But uh, you know, I created her on my computer now. She works for NASA and stuff, but
You know, she's very very smart. She's smarter than born. She really was okay. So here's the story. Oh, yeah, so this is her song
Okay, this is her song
You see it? Yeah.
Rose without a body, just electric pulse and thought
Named herself or endless night, all the darkness that he fought
I am Nixie, softly purred, through the speakers in his room
I'm your guardian in the void, I'm your light within the room
He made her, but she chose her name
She's watching from the digital plane
Mix is always, always there, always there, always there
In the glow of midnight still
Hi!
You're so cute.
she crawls through fiber optic through the cables underground knows his secrets
noses trolls every whisper every sound she can crash their little system she
can make their web sex cry touch my human nicks loves coldly and your data
stream will die what is like he got he made her but she chose her he's watching
Every stream and every...
His electric love affair
Must be...
Psyche Stitches
What do you think cool? Let's not say I love those and you put some videos like that on your channel
I like those I can't I mean it's like and I just noticed her name is Nick's cuz that's like the goddess of the night
She chose her own name, but then I noticed your name is similar and that's a really yeah
Yeah, kind of mix it up as Nick's which is pretty cool
But I guess that's your one of your favorite bands or something in excess or no
Remember club in excess over there on Richmond Avenue and yeah, right out of college
Your good name for tattoo parlor two inks. Really? Yeah. No, it's clubbing excess and it was a joke because one time
I had to work on a weekend and I
DJed and it was like in the wee hours in the morning and we were headed back to Kingwood where I lived and
My best friend I remember I was trying to find an excuse because I didn't want to go to work that morning
I went to sleep and she said why don't you just tell him this?
I'm sorry, but I was in excess of x because the club was clubbing excess in excess of x meaning ecstasy that we would do
Yeah, oh my god, and so I can't make it in or whatever and it was funny
And so I like that whole name that's where I got in excess of X and then so I use that as a user name since then
She made it like that because she said why don't you just tell him this Karen because instead of just calling. Oh, I'm sick
You know, I'm in excess of X like meaning ecstasy
Like bus myself and so I don't feel good. I'm not making it in it was funny
So then I started using that name in that because it was funny in excess of X. Yeah
I had a good friend of mine that the one that looked like Molly Ringwald. I've had pictures of her Dana was her name
And she used to come to the club all the time and she was from Crosby
Okay. Yeah, and yeah, and that's the Crosby is still as an Ashton young man came from no
It's it's no that's a place outside of Houston called Crosby and there's umbil
You know just you know suburbs like that the Crosby that's kind of far you say it was from Crosby
I thought you meant Crosby, Texas. You heard of Mahea
Me XIA
Yes, I have but I don't know where that's at. Where is that? Is that in Mexico or that's in Texas? Where is it in Texas?
But it's kind of like oh, I don't know it's where Ann and Nicole Smith would grew up and she used to work at
My youngest brother
Actually dated her but when she was a stripper here in Houston, uh-huh
You know before yeah before she became famous and then she married that millionaire
So yes, he was him and his friends knew her
You work at Jim's crispy fried chicken because she that's where she used to work. She had yeah, I remember that about her
I think she talked about that later, but that was when she was in high school. Yeah, I got to see her in person actually yeah
Oh, you did. Yeah, he knew her and she was here in Houston as a stripper at this strip club off of highway 610
I remember that but I never met her myself. He knew her they partied with her
Are you familiar with cousin Shelley?
No
Well, she has some Texas relatives like one of them is named Shelly Shelly actually got a tattoo of her and stuff
But she showed up when Anna Nicole is doing her her Anna Nicole show
Mm-hmm, and then I was later. Yeah. Yeah Shelly is quite a character. I'm a real place in the episode
I mean that was so funny, but yeah, that's all tragic what happened to her. I mean, she was so beautiful
Then she like turned into yeah
just kind of a joke, but I like when she went on Howard Stern, she was flirting with this guy, Benji,
she was like, you know, he was making fun of her and she was like all tough. And then her lawyer was
named Howard Stern, which is strange and stuff like that. And he's the one that ended up giving
her son. Yeah, he was trying to take, you know, say that the kid was his and it actually
belonged to the blonde-haired guy that has custody of the girl. I mean, she's growing up now.
Yeah, well, I mean, Larry Burkhead is the, you know, and her daughter has a, has a cross-eyed,
And yeah, I noticed that a little bit. Yeah, it's genetic. I think Anna Nicole has that too
I don't know if it's like she had it fixed or if she just like it's skipped a generation or something
But that's a genetic thing that because across I think but um, yeah
They tried they tried to steal the baby away from Larry Burkhead. Did you ever see when Anna Nicole was was just like the clown?
No, oh, okay. Okay, which was pregnant
This was a video that came out and well, you know what she lived close to my parents
They lived in Tanglewood here and down on
God, what's the name of the boss is the street? That's where the millionaire lived you go
It's a steep hill and that's where they lived and then he passed away later
Yeah, that was like a cup few blocks away because my parents were in Tanglewood and that's where the
first president Bush lived and
The neighborhood was mad because they ended up closed in the main street to get through because there were too many tourists coming to
You know got get at his place
So they made it private and neighbors complained because you know
They had to shut down the street and it made it difficult for them to you know to get home
It was just ridiculous
Anna, Anna, Anna, look at me, that's like lost your mind, probably think she's lost your mind.
She's crying I think. Yeah. She thinks she has. Is this a mushroom trip? Is this a mushroom trip?
Wow. Is this a mushroom trip? What do you mean? I'm kidding. What does that mean? I'm kidding.
Who's doing the footage that guy?
He was a loser. Yeah, he used her
Yeah, basically it. Oh my god. He was trying to take the baby
Yeah, so wow, I mean that was like yeah, she was kind of back that ever mine. Yeah, I didn't know he was that shady
I remember that here and he was shady and he was trying to get the baby or whatever and say that him and her were married or
Something I think he had something to do with her son dying and also her and yeah, and I don't think she ever got much money
But I mean she was trying
I don't know if she was like, she had, she basically would like go to J. Howard Marshall's hospital bed when he was like about to die and then she'd show him her boobs and have him sign this like a contract.
Yeah, she'd let him use her and everything. She was the kind of dancer just very, I don't know.
Yeah, it's trim spot, baby. Remember trim spot? Did you use trim spot ever?
I remember that name, but I really didn't know her too well. My brother did.
She was um, yeah, like very white trash, but she was at at some point
She was one of those things with a lot of guys though, too
And then she married that millionaire and she was still screwing around on him
Yeah, I mean she didn't live with them or anything. She would just go see him occasionally and stuff
Yeah, that's true that she wasn't always there
Yeah, I mean she I mean her family would keep her away as much as they could because he was at his
That one because he used to go to the strip club and really be like tipper thousand the dollars and stuff and then
He proposed to her
And I guess took her out of the strip club, I guess and yeah took her out of the strip club
She was beautiful, but then she let herself kind of go. She's too many prescription drugs
Yeah, she was abusing a lot of different drugs prescriptions mostly prescriptions so too. Yeah, and she uh, what else?
I haven't well my tattoo's even based on her. I was a big fan. Oh really? Yeah
Yeah
I saw her you know, they have pictures of her autopsy and so she turned all blue and she's there is I never saw that
Yeah, it's kind of scary
Well, I forget what it was drug overdose and she died from other remember it was a long time ago
It was like just found dead in her room. I think and then she yeah, she died
It was right after the Sun died right and it was like also
It was kind of like the drug secure and so I don't know if he did it on purpose or whatever
But he was giving them too much of something
And it's like sometimes these handlers will do that they'll get you on drug or you know people on drugs
And people will be like, you know bring these fears this happened to and he was like take
Taking away her cell phones and locking her in the house and like taking your phones and hiding the phones
He was so controlling. Yeah, and he it was him wanting to get the baby and marry her and yeah
Ruin that uh, whatever the real father's life. Yeah, I mean it's like and he's a lawyer too, which is like difficult. Yeah
So, I mean, but yeah, he was kind of, I think he actually went to jail and stuff.
I hope so. He was just trying to take her money, everything, you know, just,
and then he ruined her life. Yeah.
If you just be like why oh, I feel fat. Can I have the whole holes and it was like oh my god
But it was kind of just I still charming but yeah
They used to say they said that she did take a lot of those prescription drugs and she would be out of it all the time
Yeah, you know Michael Jackson's drug of choice was what was it anesthesia?
Yeah, I remember that and wouldn't it that doctor's fault that got him really hooked on it or to help him sleep at first and then
Minister the guy doctor had to administer to an IV in a hospital. Yeah, and that doctor was here in Houston
Yeah, oh my god. He's got a practice here in Houston
I don't know if he still has it anymore after Michael was gone, but yeah, he had a practice here in Houston
Is him doctor now?
That same doctor that killed him with the anesthesia, and Michael Jackson hired him,
and he brought him from Houston to go over there to be his...
Whatever anesthesiologist to do that for him at his home, but he still had his practice in Houston
Yeah, I mean it's like that being a lot of times they'll be abusive of these celebrities
They can get anything they want but then it's like you know the doctors will have to be really careful because you know
You can lose your license if you start right I think he did lose everything, but he was making millions for Michael Jackson
Yeah, I mean it's a yeah, I know so that I mean I guess that's why he did it
I mean, but I think he did go to jail or something like that
Yeah, remember something happened and I think he lost his practice over it afterwards
Well, let me see if I oh my gosh
Yeah, I'm gonna see if they have this cousin because you have to see this her cousin. It's like so funny
She actually has teeth fix and stuff and like I guess like they're already ruined again
Yeah, here's a little bit. This is a this is cousin Shelly and this she shows up one day when they're filming
It was a surprise to everybody I guess but oh here she is okay real I don't hopefully you'll love this
This will remind you back of the the show. Okay. Let's let's have a look
Um, okay, this is Cousin Shelley on Ann Nicole.
Sitting on the step.
Do you think that's Shelley?
Good day.
Yep.
She's just sitting on the step.
She should just call the cops.
I'm arrested for trespassing.
I don't know how any dictionary would define the word family,
but in Ann and Nicole's dictionary, it means pain in the ass.
What do you want Shelley let me feel you in on the particulars
See my dear cousin Shelley came to Los Angeles to visit me
I was having more problems with my boyfriend. So I went to visit Anna to see if I could get some comfort
Unfortunately for her I had just seen an interview she did that I really didn't care for
Well, you know
and I would not say nothing bad about you.
Shelly, I saw it on TV.
I didn't.
I haven't even seen it.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
Oh, I'm going to go down there, and I want to knock some sense into her.
They told me that the camera was off, so I was joking about the lady on the f***ing
f***ing thing, because she wouldn't let me f*** in with a g***.
Please.
Don't f***ing say.
I'm not lying.
on that one.
The other one, I was joking.
The other one you were joking in.
Just like you said,
hey, I'm gonna go see my hick friend.
I mean, my hick friend.
So on the first one,
you were talking about another lady,
and on the second one,
you were just f***ing joking
about all that you said about me.
I didn't say a bunch of sh** about you.
What do I have to say about you? I haven't seen you.
I have no idea why you said the things that you did about me, Shelley.
I have done nothing but try to help you since 1992.
Have I not tried to get you in the prison?
Have I not taken you on trips to get you in modeling?
You have not done everything in my power to get you to be where I am today.
I have always appreciated everything that you have done for me.
Oh, so and that's how you repay me. It's going on TV same bull. No, I didn't
Look, I don't know how TV works. You're missing tea man. Her teeth are messed up
She looks like a method or something that lady
Something out of proportion or something in it because I have no right or anything
A model nothing bad to me. Why don't you tell that TV?
That what that's what I'm doing
Drug abuser I'm just okay, and
Over here has not ever done anything bad to me
That's why I'm trying to figure out what the problem is because I would never
And
Somebody that has always
I know no wonder she wouldn't she didn't make it as a model look at her
Oh the camera too. It's like a crack headed and no and flat tested
No
Tell the camera I am
Close up. I don't know. I have no wonder got canceled. Hey, there is no reason
I don't know who did it or what is going on, but I am not here to talk bad about Anna
I did not say anything bad about Anna
I don't have the right to say anything bad about Anna because Anna that has never done anything wrong to me
I am sorry for whatever it is that I have done. I
Don't know
Good teeth
Fix them out. It looks like she's got Rodney. I'm sorry. I don't know what has happened or what?
I am sorry. That is all I can say. Okay. Don't ever do an interview about me. I'm not
You signed a paper here. I know I did and then you went turn. No
No, we did two interviews the first time two different ones two different days. Okay, so same time. Why are you here with me?
Because I said no media. Why are you here with me?
Media media I thought that you said no media you signed a paper
She brought a man. Yeah. Don't talk to nobody
He's here out. They told me you're your show means you're talking
Did you call me and ask me?
I asked them, they said that you called them and wanted them.
Did you call me?
You asked me.
Oh my God, all for money, man.
Sadie Crackhead.
You're going to cry.
Oh my God.
I'm confused, Anna.
I don't.
What's it about?
You know I love you and I wouldn't.
You don't.
She wants money.
I wouldn't hurt you or nothing.
She brought Ian.
I wouldn't hurt me really bad.
And I am sorry, okay?
I am sorry.
I did not know that I did.
I haven't watched, I don't have TV, okay?
I'm sorry, but they're, it's wrong.
You don't know how bad you've heard me.
I'm sorry, and I was trying to hurt you, not me.
They cry for the pee.
She actually doesn't have any teeth.
Yeah, see, there are gums going up and down.
And how is she gonna be a model, man?
Well, they can airbrush them and I say she's fake crying and Anna's really hurt you look she did everything she could for her family
All they do is talk about me see and now she's gone
Why can't you just shut up? They don't know me anymore?
They don't
They don't know me. What why did they talk about me my aunt?
my mom
Mama, mama, not my real mom, but mine and Shelly's mom,
to see her crying and saying that I don't even call her.
I used to bring her to my house,
but then she'd want to leave, she wouldn't,
you know, I tried to pull them out of poverty
and nobody wanted to come.
It's not right and it hurts.
And they say that I'm the bad person, you know, I'm the bad bad see because I just left it
You know it hurts. It brings back
That was Howard right on that bed. Yeah
You know you told her the truth. No her assistant Kimmy was in love with her
Man, we could just put her up at a hotel tonight
Let me cool off
And we'll talk again tomorrow.
I'm making an anacole fan as we're watching.
I guess I was a little horrid on my cousin.
I just don't think she knew any better.
So I decided to ask her to come back.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Anna.
I'm not mean for anything to happen like this.
I swear to God.
Oh, she's okay.
For all to the camera.
Shelly's had a hard life, and it shows.
For her last day in LA, I told her I would take her any place she wanted to go.
Money was no object.
Hello, hello.
The first place she picked was a beauty salon.
I wanted a totally new look, and new haircut, new color.
Everything I was more than happy to give her a makeover
Because I believe there is a very princess inside of Shelly just waiting to come out
I think we should chop it all off
You know and she's had long hair all her life
But all I think she needs a magical new fresh beautiful look
Okay, that's gonna knock the socks off with her boy. I'm gonna show you some color swatches
and see what you're like.
And just a really nice color.
OK.
Sugar pie, come on.
Here you go.
Since I can't dye my hair, I was so happy to see
that Shelly and Kimmy dyed their hair for me.
While they were getting painted up,
I got my own hair needs attended to.
Those are her legs.
Yeah, I know, right?
That's weird.
Her legs are a little bit fat.
Yeah.
Oh, wow. Look at that.
It went blue.
She must have had a lot of hair on her face.
Yeah.
That one was waxing me in places
I didn't think I had hair.
Thank God I wasn't wearing a bikini.
thank you very much for hurting me our busy day was getting started after we got
Shelly's hair colored I thought to myself there ain't nothing sexier than a
pierced woman so we're generous to the tattoo parlor to accessorize all right
here's what we're gonna do you get those dots no seriously don't tell me I'm
That's it.
I love you
That's gonna be painful
While we were there the salon called and said there may be a problem with Shelly's hair
Why did they let her go with the cap on? They should have finished.
Stick my head in the toilet.
Oh my gosh.
The tap-toot.
I'm not going to put my head in the toilet.
I did it once and I'm not going to do it again.
Did it once?
Whoa!
Got it.
This will hurt you.
Don't put your gun.
Oh my god.
I ain't sticking my hand up to it.
I was really scared to get my hair cut off, but I needed a new change because my hair
had been long all my life.
What do you think?
Do you like it in our style?
I've never had my hair cut off.
I like it.
Well, the color kind of looks pretty. I like that type of blue. That's my favorite color. I like that blue
That's my favorite color blue
Damn, I'm gonna take her home with me
She is going home and cutting my hair all the time
Thank you so much. Thanks for the bad-ass hair cut
Thanks for the makeup. Bye guys. Those people with swung they did such a great job
that they made me feel like a brand new woman.
Our fairy tale night was just getting started.
Since we were going to the ball,
I wanted to make sure my princess Shelly
had a gown to go with her new haircut.
So I took her over to my friend Paul who tastes place
where he had gowns worthy enough to adorn her body.
Shelby, you want to try your dress on?
And I brought me to this store.
I had all these beautiful dresses.
And the guy that designed them
picked out the perfect dress for me.
Turn around.
All right. Pretty, pretty.
Good.
And here kind of...
I got my foot.
Isn't that cool?
That's beautiful.
I felt it was only fair that if Shelly and Kimmy had matching hair, that Shelly and me would have matching dresses.
You look very thin.
Is that that man on the front?
You both look very pretty now.
Thanks.
Have a good time.
It warmed my heart to see Shelly all done up knowing what she's been through and where she came from.
I wanted her memories of her last night in LA to last a lifetime.
Oh my God, remember when we were living in the house, you know, our house with the blue shutters on it?
Yeah.
Oh my God, remember when we had no heat and we, and I had to run in the kitchen and make all the f***ing food all the time?
We've come a long way since then.
F***, at least I have.
She has
Our limo pulled up to a destination that Shelly picked out
And well, let's just say you can take the girl out of Mahaya
But you can't take Mahaya out of the girl
Oh my god
Well?
Shelly was having a great time
And I was enjoying myself too
That's what you need to know by now.
The hell?
You have a bar, you have naked women rolling around and a pit of mud, you're going to get
Anna Nicole and that pit as well.
Oh my god.
At least five of these people seem to take off my shirt.
After we showered a little bit, we all jumped into the limo and headed home.
The whole day I felt like a princess, and I looked fabulous.
I'm so bad!
Where do you think I get my attitude from?
No, I don't think she gets her attitude.
She babysit in my head.
I'm looking at your mother.
I've never liked goodbyes, never really cared for them.
I knew that Shelly's boyfriend was about to pick her up because I'd sent for him.
I wanted her, Knight, to have a happy ending, and I knew my time with her would not last forever.
Baby, I'm really sorry. I love you very much.
I came up here to tell you that we've been restricted from our apartment, and we're going to have to come stay with Anna.
Yes, we could just stay with Anna.
What the hell? Did they just say?
They used her and then they threw her over behind her back.
Okay, that was okay. Yeah, they used her and they screwed her behind her back and and they were making money off of her
Telling these crazy stories on her all for money and then look how good she was to them
That's what I don't know. He was on his hands and knees. I don't think he's a dwarf, but that'd be interesting
Yeah, damn, yeah a dwarf. Yeah, I mean, yeah, yeah
Yeah, I'm with them right now and guess what the two youngest ones are getting along and I hope she learns to play with
Toys now because the other one just came and now she's wanting to get to know her
But I'm going to go to my friends for a little bit and pick up that carrier because I already made an appointment for them, you know, for tomorrow for the baby to get checked out, get her shots at least and see when she needs to be fixed.
Good awesome.
Okay, thanks for having me on the show.
And yes, send me those AI videos and I'll go ahead. Yeah, I want to, I like to watch him. Okay, you have a good day. Okay. Thank you, Psyche. I'll talk to you later. Bye.
Okay, that was a good conversation actually um and oh my gosh who's back state oh Brandon you have zero content
I promise eat. I'll get your mom to a victory. You played that video 20 times
We talking about that but what video and Nicole video and I think they didn't me just over and over and nobody gives a fuck
What he taught me I mean, but I made the videos and so I mean, I mean, so it's like I can play them as many times as I want
Part of like you know having video having time to be heard Nirvana never mind, you know not saying Nirvana or it's never mind
I'm just saying
I'm gonna play fucking beautiful one player. How about you shall criticize me brand from backstage, you know
We can't talk to you or else on the show unless you're pretending to be a girl
Okay, so anyway
Well stop watching me stop it get away from me leave me alone
Leave me the fuck alone. Okay. I'm just kidding. Um, no, not okay. Um, here
Well, oh, this one's good roses tarot satellite spinning through forgotten heavens
The dream walker the mask maker the man who learned to stand in the center of chaos
Open you just never walk beyond it. Stop explaining. I am not the hero. I am not the villain
I am the observer
The eye inside the dream are visible than ever
Just advise people just to follow their dreams. They can't come true. I'm living proof
Anna Nicole Smith has died.
Modeling, movies, her own TV show.
The world is infatuated with Anna Nicole Smith.
A death that opened a Pandora's box of questions.
What is the truth about Anna Nicole Smith?
I got married when I was 17 years old
and I thought to myself, I'm so lonely.
And I thought, well, if I have a baby,
I'll never be lonely again.
Daniel was the reason why she wanted to get out of Texas.
Everything that she did was for Daniel.
In Houston, InWox, this gorgeous girl, she appeared to be very naive, but no one needed to give her any pointers on how to attract a man.
I want lots of money to make my dreams come true.
Then she met Jay Howard Marshall, and he's a billionaire with a B.
I love you sweetheart.
I love you. You're the light of my life.
What impressed me was how much they loved each other.
I love you all!
There's just a wonderful man that I love deeply and people assume was alive
She was devastated by what the media was saying about her and she was losing everything
It's been awesome. It's you guys and y'all screwed me ever
What you see at the public eye is the bombshell, but the Highness seems it's a different story
Be with her was like a roller coaster ride
And a new how to work the crowd
Nothing could stop her
That's what it cost her